Seeker: [dishes clanking] You said it's multicolored?
DM: Yep.
Unknown: Is that different from the other one?
DM: No.
Unknown: Do you have a teacup yet?
DM: No, I don't have a teacup.
Unknown: Oh, okay.
DM: Okay. Thank you.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: [dishes clanking] Oh, wait.
DM: We need music. [gentle music]
DM: So you have a few minutes to discuss out of character what you wanna do, and then we're rolling initiative.
DM: [gentle music]
Unknown: Tear away to the center.
Unknown: Cut it open. [coughs]
Seeker: Leviathan mode or no?
Delwath: Um, [coughs] I probably think you should stay in Leviathan mode because-
Unknown: Yeah
Delwath: ... you're practically immune to its damage.
Unknown: Um, we'll talk about it.
Delwath: Like, what are you gonna do, punch it?
Unknown: Right.
Unknown: Um,
Delwath: I'm feeling like Del- like the damage output from the Leviathan is pretty weak compared to Delwath's damage output.
Unknown: So-
DM: Um, thank you
Unknown: ... it's nice from the like,
Seeker: a, a immune to damage perspective apparently
Delwath: [dishes clanking] But, um, just... Coming down the smites scale armor damage.
Unknown: [dishes clanking]
Wellby: Is it not that we need to do anything different than just dump a whole bunch of damage to get into the center?
Wellby: Like we...
Wellby: Who knows if some... Is there a different way to attack the problem?
Seeker: Well, [clears throat] I think I can swim through
Unknown: to this direction.
Unknown: So we'll have to test that.
Unknown: I mean,
Unknown: possibly
Unknown: the idea is that
Unknown: everybody, uh,
DM: fights it while Seeker tries to swim.
Delwath: Like we fight towards the thing, and Seeker tries to go
Unknown: more into it and get the
Unknown: whatever it's guarding.
Unknown: Just retrieve it and then-
Unknown: And retrieve it.
Unknown: See if we can-
Delwath: See if we can bypass its defenses more easily-
Unknown: Right
Unknown: ... as Leviathan.
Unknown: I like that.
Kenzo: But we have to kill the thing in the middle, right?
Unknown: Well, uh, is that...
Unknown: Maybe I'll get it out.
Unknown: Right.
DM: Get what out?
Unknown: Whatever that thing is.
Delwath: The nodule of chaos that caused this whole problem.
Kenzo: Oh, so we think it's like an actual, like physical artifact?
Wellby: We need to like-
DM: Water organ
Wellby: ... like to x-ray the whole thing to understand.
Kenzo: Well, it's kind of, kind of how the...
Kenzo: Yeah. I'm sure we have the right kind of a metal mapper at least.
Seeker: We need to do the high res version of this.
DM: No, yeah. The, the like two little orbiting bits of...
DM: That's what you were sensing in the middle of the well, and that's presumably what's in the middle of this.
DM: It was, yeah.
Wellby: Is it like, is that like a battery that we can take out, or do we have to like destroy the whole of the thing out there?
DM: Kenzo's sense of it was it is a,
DM: it is a crystallized fragment of limbo that presumably must be destroyed in order to...
DM: Otherwise, anytime water gets in the cistern it'll just create another Unus.
Unknown: So basically...
Delwath: Right. So, so we send...
Delwath: But we don't know how to destroy it just yet.
Wellby: Can you banish an object
Wellby: back to its home dimension?
Unknown: Good question.
Unknown: I mean,
Unknown: could hold onto it and plane shift.
Seeker: Oh, drop it off and plane shift back.
Unknown: Yeah. I mean-
Wellby: You can't rainbow bridge back, but we could plane shift back?
Delwath: Uh, if Seeker come, if Seeker comes he can use a wand.
Unknown: Yeah.
Delwath: Actually, that suggests kind of one strategy would be for Seeker and Delwath to run towards the thing, try and get to the crystal center
Unknown: as Leviathans,
Delwath: grab onto the crystal center, plane shift to Limbo, and then plane shift back.
Wellby: Can you plane shift an unwilling creature or?
DM: No.
Wellby: Hm.
DM: We probably have to cut it out somehow.
Unknown: Also, do I have a wand?
Unknown: Not
Unknown: a spell.
Delwath: You'd have to turn into Delwath and then plane shift us.
Unknown: Hm.
Kenzo: We're gonna need to use your wand. We cannot go Leviathan anymore.
Unknown: Right.
Unknown: [dishes clanking]
Unknown: But it's unclear,
Delwath: it's very unclear if this thing is
Unknown: more like an organ
Delwath: that we would have to somehow cut out-
Unknown: Or a magic item
Unknown: ... or more like a,
Unknown: an item.
Wellby: Or if it can't be separated from the rest of the creature whatsoever.
Delwath: Right. Can Kenzo tell actually?
Unknown: The what?
Unknown: I mean, it's a...
DM: Yes, from Kenzo's perspective, it is a...
DM: It is, it is like the driver mutation of a cancerous tumor
Seeker: So if we drop it in the Green Sea and wait a few years, the entire Green Sea will be ooze.
Unknown: Yes.
Wellby: That'd be amazing.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: But it's probably, like, you can't...
DM: I mean, you can't just pick it up, right?
Unknown: Right.
Unknown: It's probably, like...
Unknown: It's more like an organ.
DM: It's more like an organ than it is a...
DM: It's not like an item that's surrounded by ooze.
Wellby: Yeah. Yeah.
DM: To the extent the ooze has any internal structure, whatever, which it might have a lot of.
Unknown: We don't know.
DM: It's... I mean, you saw, right, that it was creating all these little filamentous strands.
DM: So it's possible that it's, like, surrounded by an acid net that will restrain you if you try and get close or anything, something like that.
Wellby: Right.
Wellby: And so that all serves to just kill the ooze and then
Wellby: deal with the thing once the ooze is dead?
Unknown: Well, I guess...
Wellby: But if you, you know, if it's the Dread Mutagen, then
Wellby: the rest of it's already grown.
Wellby: Like...
Unknown: But it's unclear...
Wellby: Like, we'd still have to kill the ooze even if we took the thing out of the center of it.
Unknown: That's the question, yeah.
Wellby: Which is...
Unknown: Well, I don't know.
Wellby: Is that the analogy you're making, Tim?
Delwath: The other ooze turned to crystal when we cut its connection.
DM: If you get r-
Unknown: Really?
DM: Yes. Like, possibly it will just turn to crystal if you
DM: get this thing out, but I'm just saying you c- I wouldn't expect you to be able to just swim into the middle of it and-
Wellby: Yeah
DM: ... lift it out, right?
DM: You're gonna have to do a significant amount of damage to
DM: cut... Like, you would have to cut it out, right?
DM: Like...
Seeker: I wonder if there's a way magically to slice a section of space
Seeker: and m- move it somewhere else, so like Wall of Stone kind of cuts through space.
Seeker: Any plane makes a door in space.
Seeker: What are the other things? Ooh, we have, like, a...
Seeker: to sort of extract something.
DM: So your wand...
Seeker: Oh, can that make an interplanar slice?
DM: So you could just make another w- another wound to Limbo, and then we could run last, yesterday's adventure all over again.
Seeker: [laughs] That's not so bad.
Unknown: Love it.
Wellby: Uh...
Delwath: Wait, so you need a spell, but you c- you still have your wish, right?
Unknown: That's-
DM: What? No
Seeker: ... a thing we could do.
Unknown: Seeker still has his wish?
Unknown: Oh, no. No, no, no, no, no.
DM: No. Shape change.
Unknown: You used shape change.
Unknown: Oh, that's right. Yeah.
Unknown: You used it on the wish.
Wellby: We have a Scroll of Wish and we have a genie in a bottle.
DM: You have a Scroll of Wish.
Seeker: The genie... What can the genie in a bottle do?
DM: It has a 10% chance of trying to kill you, a 10% chance of granting you a wish, and a 9- and an 80% chance of
DM: obeying your commands for one hour.
Unknown: Genie. That's pretty cool.
Wellby: It's pretty wonder- just to have an ally on the field.
Unknown: I like that.
DM: But remember, it's also an efreet.
Unknown: We should save it.
Unknown: It's, it's fire.
Unknown: For Plane of Fire.
Unknown: Oh, yeah, yeah.
DM: No, I mean if you want to learn something about the Plane of Fire, it's a person to talk to.
Unknown: Um,
Delwath: Scroll of Wish is definitely something we could use.
Unknown: Well...
Unknown: And then, um...
Kenzo: I think my attitude is if we got items, let's fucking use them.
Unknown: Yeah.
Kenzo: If we wanna have... If we, if we have saves
Unknown: ... now is the time.
Unknown: Like,
Unknown: spend your bardics, you know.
Kenzo: Well, that, that last adventure, Tim was like-
Unknown: We could use, um...
Kenzo: I was gonna say, Ti- Tim was like, "Y- you know you've got this potion of...
Unknown: Like, check, check your inventory,"
Unknown: Yeah
Kenzo: ... and I was like, "What's in my inventory?" I was like, "Oh, fuck, I can turn into a dragon."
Kenzo: He's like, "Yeah, sure you wanna, you know, do that?"
Kenzo: Like, I was, like, debating whether or not to use it, and then at some point I was like, "Fuck it, just use it."
Unknown: Yeah.
Unknown: Well, I still have my invulnerability.
Unknown: We could use disintegrate.
Unknown: It's a sixth level spell.
Delwath: If the creature is huge or larger, the spell disintegrates a 10 foot cube portion of it.
Wellby: That's interesting.
Seeker: Versus telekinesis will lift it out.
Wellby: Or even, like, disintegrating our way in.
Unknown: Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Wellby: Like, if it's a crystallized piece of another plane, maybe disintegrate doesn't apply to the-
Unknown: Or it does
Unknown: ... itself, right?
Delwath: ... things in the material plane.
Unknown: Yes.
Kenzo: How far in is it from where we are?
Unknown: Like, we're at the surface.
DM: So okay. So let's set the scene bef- right, and then you're gonna roll initiative.
DM: You are s- so there's a, there's a pit that's c- there's like...
DM: So there's the cistern beneath the city that was once the, like, magical waters of Isingue, right?
DM: The... And there are wells.
DM: The w- the center well has collapsed, and so now there's a drop that goes down about 40 feet, just, like, rum- like,
DM: all the pillars have collapsed, the dirt has fallen in.
DM: There's just, like, rubble,
DM: um, below you
DM: sloping down, so it, like, makes a...
DM: It's like a sinkhole in the middle of the plaza, basically.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: The ooze itself is, like, 400 feet big, but the center of the ooze is at the bottom of that 40 foot drop, and then it has all these, like, tendrils that
DM: are climbing up out of the, out of the pit.
DM: So imagine... Like, imagine a crater like this, like a sloped descent in a big circle.
DM: It's at the center of that, and there's, like, a fair bit of mass around it.
DM: There's... Like, it's...
DM: The ooze itself is, like, bubbling 30 feet up from the
DM: bottom of the ground, so there's at least, like, 30 feet of density of just ooze.
DM: It's almost more like an environment than a creature itself, right?
DM: And it's sending out long tendrils, like, 100 feet in each direction around the center of this collapsed
DM: mass. [coughs]
Wellby: Uh, what are its immunities and resistances again?
Unknown: Immune to, like, everything.
Unknown: Resistant to everything.
DM: So it is immune to acid, necrotic poison.
DM: It's resistant to everything.
Unknown: [laughs]
DM: Charmed, exhausted, frightened, grappled, paralyzed, petrified, poisoned, prone, restrained, stunned, unconscious.
DM: Has blind sight. It's not immune to incapacitated.
Unknown: Oh.
DM: That's the only thing it's not immune to.
DM: [laughs]
Unknown: And
Seeker: w- its weakest saves?
DM: Uh, its, its weakest save is charisma.
DM: Strongest save is con.
Kenzo: Um, but the... This density,
Kenzo: where, where is that? It's, like, kinda-
DM: In the, in the middle.
Unknown: But how far down? How many feet?
DM: It's, like, 30 feet down.
DM: There's, like, a blob that's, like, a 30 foot by 30 foot cube in the middle of the sinkhole.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: And that's the thickest part of the ooze.
Unknown: Got it.
DM: And the nodule's, like, in the middle of that.
Kenzo: Got it. Guys, you know what we're fighting?
Kenzo: Like, this is, I think, the best analogy.
Kenzo: It literally is, um, the fucking ending of Akira.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: Mm.
Unknown: Oh my God, that movie.
Unknown: Yeah.
Unknown: That's what this is.
Unknown: Wow.
Seeker: So banishment [clears throat] is a charisma save.
Unknown: I mean, we could just...
Kenzo: That's good 'cause it'll... They could burn legendary resistance instead of these if you try to banish it.
Unknown: Right.
DM: Well-
Unknown: It just-
DM: You only have banishment through your wand, right?
Unknown: I mean, I can cast Banish.
Seeker: I have seven charges of Banishment through the wand.
DM: No, but I mean you can't use your wand while you're cracked.
Unknown: Well, we're alive. We'll be fine.
Delwath: But it also comes back when banishment ends.
Delwath: Although, if the target is...
Kenzo: But it also makes it use the, use up its, its resistances.
Unknown: Yeah, yeah,
Delwath: yeah. It's unclear, I guess, if it would come back or if it counts as...
DM: Yeah, is it one of those types where you
DM: Uh, not
DM: according to the time sheet, it is not native to Limbo.
Seeker: Right. Right. So is it an aberration, a celestial, an elemental, a fey, or a fiend?
DM: No, it's an ooze.
Unknown: Yeah. Oh, that's a whole category.
DM: That's a whole creature type.
Unknown: So, yeah.
DM: It was created by the magic of the Limbo contamination.
DM: It was created by a Limbo contamination-
Unknown: No, but it's native to the Material Plane
DM: ... but it's, it's actually...
DM: Fundamental material is the Waters of Isingue.
Seeker: Mm. So it would come back from banishment.
DM: Yes.
Seeker: We could try imprisonment.
Unknown: Using the Scroll of Wish.
Unknown: Or just make-
DM: No, imprisonment is a 9th level spell
Seeker: No, we could try it using the Bindings.
DM: It would cost a minute to cast.
Unknown: Yeah. But I'm not-
Delwath: I, I, I think, I think we need to just, I think we need to just fight it, right?
DM: Well, right now you need to roll initiative 'cause it is attacking you.
Seeker: So we cannot use imprisonment.
DM: It's not just waiting for you to, like, do whatever you want to it.
Unknown: Right.
DM: So roll initiative.
Unknown: All right.
Unknown: So the other ooze
Seeker: seems to focus its attacks on the thing that it noticed was attacking it.
Unknown: Mm-hmm.
Seeker: Which suggests to me that I should use Summon Construct to have a separate target to-
Unknown: Oh, yeah. That's a great idea
DM: The two things the other ooze did that you might want to remember is it had...
DM: It managed to c- make itself resistant to a certain damage type
DM: and it focused attacks on whoever had last attacked it.
DM: But whether this thing does the same thing, I don't know.
Unknown: Tim, you want this last little bit here?
DM: No, I'm good. I still have some on my plate.
Unknown: But only two-
Unknown: Mike, any more?
Unknown: No, I had the last bite. I'm good.
Unknown: All right. I'm just gonna do this.
Wellby: To a certain damage type?
DM: Well, that was what the other ooze did.
Unknown: Yeah.
Unknown: Wait.
Seeker: It... So wait, it could switch to one-
DM: Yeah
Unknown: ... damage type.
Unknown: Oh, and I can't hear my initiative.
Unknown: Well, I-
Unknown: I'm modifying damage
Delwath: ... cannot use your wand in the land, but okay.
DM: Okay, initiative. [rolls dice] Uh, uh, what's my plus?
DM: It's just, uh,
DM: 7. 21.
Unknown: 30 for me.
Unknown: 30.
Unknown: Oh, yeah.
Unknown: 19.
Unknown: 15.
Wellby: [laughs] No, plus 7 is, uh...
Unknown: Uh, it's 25.
Unknown: Oh, 20. Sorry.
Kenzo: Oh, yeah. I got a, um, also a really high
Seeker: initiative modifier is 20.
Unknown: Wait, should we bring up the Paraceratops?
Unknown: Oh, 31.
DM: Can't. Seven-day recharge.
Unknown: Oh.
DM: 31?
Unknown: Yeah. I rolled an 18.
Unknown: I have a plus 13.
Wellby: The, uh, the fly we can see if we bring out, but the fly is not exactly a friend yet.
Unknown: Right.
DM: Sorry, who was 21? Seeker was 20 and Delwath was 21?
Unknown: Kenzo's 31.
DM: Are you gonna switch?
Unknown: Uh, do you want- Wait, what's our order?
Unknown: Kenzo-
DM: Kenzo, Wellby, Delwath, Seeker
Unknown: ...
Delwath: I mean, should, should just, should, uh, Kenzo go first so that everybody...
Delwath: Oh, no, it doesn't matter 'cause everybody gets...
Unknown: Everybody gets what?
Delwath: You'll get advantage on your second round if [coughs] this versus your first round.
Unknown: Because I'm in melee.
Wellby: Uh [coughs] e- everyone gets advantage once.
DM: Everyone gets advantage one, on one turn.
Wellby: Whether you go before me or after me, it doesn't matter.
DM: Yeah.
Unknown: You'll get advantage on the next one.
Wellby: I think the sort of mechanic... I don't know.
Wellby: Maybe it's simpler for me to go first, but, uh...
Unknown: But then
Unknown: you'll get [inhales]...
Delwath: Well, you don't get sneak attack unless there's allies.
Unknown: Or you steady aim.
Unknown: If you steady aim-
Wellby: Wait, how far up was the, um, was Vindr Sharna when it attacked?
DM: 600 feet.
Unknown: Uh, that's too far.
Delwath: But there's not much upside in not steady aiming because you have nothing else to do with your bonus action.
Unknown: Uh, true.
Delwath: 'Cause attacking twice isn't r- I mean, sure, you could get, do another 1D6.
Unknown: Yeah.
Kenzo: Advantage for me is fucking, like-
Unknown: Yeah, yeah.
Unknown: ... massively awesome
Unknown: ... 50/50.
Unknown: Okay, so you go first.
DM: Okay, so it's-
Unknown: What'd you roll for initiative?
DM: 30.
Unknown: 31.
DM: 31.
Unknown: [laughs]
Unknown: 31. What'd you get?
Unknown: 30.
Wellby: [laughs]
Kenzo: [laughs] And you thought you were going to get ridiculous initiative.
Wellby: [laughs] I really thought I had it this time, Kenzo.
Kenzo: Well, this is a plus... I, this is because it's the level 20 thing.
Kenzo: My, my, my initiative modifier used to be plus 11.
Kenzo: Now it's plus 13.
Wellby: [laughs]
Kenzo: What's your, what's your modifier?
Wellby: Only plus 11.
Kenzo: Eh.
Wellby: I know. Yeah, I'm slowing down.
Kenzo: You are slowing down.
Kenzo: Old age.
DM: Okay. So Kenzo, or sorry, Wellby.
DM: You're now, you're cur- uh, it's gonna be...
DM: The battle map is a little bit complicated, but you're currently presumably something like,
DM: uh, 200 feet away from it as you step through the...
Kenzo: Oh, because we can see-
Wellby: Oh, to the edge of the-
Delwath: 'Cause that's like the edge, 'cause it's like 400 feet.
Kenzo: We're probably like 100 feet away, right?
Kenzo: When the edge of the-
DM: Oh, yeah, yeah. You're 100 feet away
Delwath: ... it's 600 feet... It's 300 feet across, right?
DM: Yeah.
Kenzo: I mean, 600 feet across
Wellby: How tall is that? Is it all the way up?
DM: Is what?
Wellby: Is it like a sphere of clearness-
DM: High
Wellby: ... or is it a column of clearness?
DM: Uh, it's a, it's a column.
DM: It, like, goes up pretty high.
Wellby: Mm.
DM: But yeah, you're... It's, the ooze itself is like 300 feet across
DM: and
DM: is moving towards the river, so it's bi- it's biased towards the river.
DM: And you are at the riverside, so the ooze is 200 feet away from the-
Kenzo: Okay
DM: ... clear spot.
Kenzo: We come out, we're 200 feet away.
DM: You come out, you're 200 feet away from it.
Kenzo: Well...
DM: Wellby?
Wellby: I...
DM: Our planning is planned.
DM: We're gonna do what we're gonna do.
Kenzo: We're just gonna attack it, right?
DM: Yeah.
Kenzo: Attack and try to get to the middle.
Wellby: What was the planning that we did again?
Kenzo: [laughs] We didn't. That's...
Wellby: [laughs]
Kenzo: Kenzo's like, "Roll initiative."
Wellby: Yeah, but we basically just like had a way-
DM: We need to get to the center and-
Wellby: Get to the middle, yeah
DM: ... get to the middle.
Kenzo: But it's like wh- it's like how we cut off the edge of the thing.
Kenzo: Like it just-
DM: Yeah
Kenzo: ... it's not smart. It's just gonna attack whoever attacked it last.
Kenzo: It's gonna try to protect itself.
Seeker: Seeker's excited to be immune to acid and will just dive right in the center.
Seeker: I can dash all the way to it on my turn, I think.
Delwath: You could also use a legendary action to move after-
DM: You can use a legendary action to move after-
Unknown: ... after everybody else
Kenzo: Right.
Seeker: So I can [coughs] before my turn.
DM: Yeah.
Kenzo: It's a little like capture the flag-ish.
Wellby: A- as a legendary turn.
Delwath: It's a legendary action. You can move after anybody's turn.
Wellby: Yeah. Uh, all right.
DM: Yeah.
Wellby: Wellby emerges,
Wellby: pauses, hovering in midair.
DM: You said it's 100 feet from us?
Wellby: Oh, but it's only-
DM: 200 feet from you.
Wellby: Okay.
DM: There's only 40 on land. Yeah.
Wellby: Takes a slow, steady breath.
Kenzo: But it'll still be over there.
Wellby: Aims for the
Wellby: ooziest part
Wellby: and... Oh, shit.
Wellby: That's not great.
Wellby: Uh, is it armored?
DM: It is not armored.
Wellby: Uh, I'm scared. It's another one, so that is, uh, 23.
DM: 23 hits.
Kenzo: 23.
Wellby: But in the sort of tone of voice that 22 might not?
DM: N- mm.
Wellby: No, 22 might not. 22 might not.
DM: You'll have to roll again. 22 we can see.
Kenzo: It is, it is strong.
Wellby: Yeah.
Kenzo: Oh.
Wellby: Okay. And I, none of my things can do anything to it, so it's gonna do some damage.
Wellby: Uh, six, six, 12, 15.
Wellby: Uh, 15 is 38.
DM: So wait, we're 200 feet away.
Wellby: Okay.
Wellby: Are there bardic inspirations to do that?
Kenzo: Not as a level five thing.
Wellby: Oh.
DM: Yeah.
Unknown: Oh, really?
Delwath: You can't use your class ability if it wants forecasting.
DM: Yeah.
Unknown: Ah, good to know.
Kenzo: So, no.
DM: So, no. Okay.
DM: Sorry, what did you roll for damage?
Wellby: 38.
Kenzo: We just went straight into this, huh? So we're, we didn't short rest.
Kenzo: We didn't do anything. We're just like-
DM: No. Yeah, but you, you can regain your ki with initiative.
Kenzo: Oh, I just... That's right
DM: ... and also heal.
Kenzo: I, that's right. So I am actually all set.
Unknown: Let me see.
Delwath: Uh, I'm gonna use a legendary action to move 40 feet closer to it.
DM: Okay.
Unknown: I'll also then...
DM: So you're both 160 feet away now.
DM: That's what it is.
DM: Uh, it is going to use a legendary action to
DM: blast
DM: Wellby with a pseudopod.
Wellby: What if instead it thinks about the next person who might cause it damage?
Unknown: [dice rolling]
Wellby: [laughs]
Kenzo: I mean, Ken-
Unknown: Rather than the last one who did.
Kenzo: Come on. Think ahead, it is.
DM: Uh, that's a range of, a reach of 600 feet.
DM: [die rolling] That's a 26.
Wellby: That's a hit.
DM: And you take 22 points of force damage.
Wellby: I, uh-
Kenzo: That's interesting
Wellby: ... at this point,
Wellby: I might as well.
DM: Yeah.
Wellby: Let's make that 11, and that's my reaction.
DM: And it also shifts
DM: and-
Wellby: Is the pseudopod now like...
Wellby: Oh, go ahead, sorry. [coughs]
DM: It comes, like you can see the ooze becoming a little bit more, um,
DM: uh, liquidy such that arrows will fly through it.
Wellby: What?
Kenzo: Oh.
DM: It is now resistant to piercing damage.
Seeker: It's just updating its resistance.
Wellby: Yeah.
Seeker: Which means it's not resistant to whatever it was resistant to before.
Kenzo: Well-
Wellby: Is there now a pseudopod like hanging out next to me, or did it like go back?
DM: No, it goes...
DM: Hits you in the face and retreats.
Wellby: All right.
Unknown: So it just has the singular damage types.
Delwath: Yeah, which is tough as leviathans.
Unknown: But so-
Kenzo: It's also omnilugent
Delwath: ... and acid, but presumably permanently immune to acid.
DM: You know it's immune to acid.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: Kenzo, you're up.
Kenzo: Yeah, uh, so when I Sol Sign it again, is it still, is it still the same immunities and resistances, or now is it...
DM: Uh, it is now resistant to piercing damage, immune to acid, necrotic poison, same other immunities, same saves.
Unknown: Okay. Well, um,
Kenzo: so I have to do superior defense again.
Kenzo: Yeah, for one minute, so I'd have to do it again.
Unknown: All right. So I'll do superior defense,
Unknown: spend three ki on that.
Unknown: Um,
Unknown: oh, I can't do that part.
DM: Is that you're resistant to all damage types but force.
DM: Is that correct?
Kenzo: Uh, let me double check. No, I think, I think it's just all, all damage types.
DM: It's all damage?
Unknown: Yeah.
Kenzo: Uh...
Kenzo: Oh, except force damage. Uh,
Kenzo: does it know that? It doesn't, it doesn't know that.
DM: It did force damage to Wellby.
Kenzo: Huh?
Kenzo: Oh. [clears throat] Um, I can't use Lunyow's Claw again, huh?
DM: No.
Kenzo: No.
Kenzo: All right. Well, I will...
Kenzo: Oh, but I haven't used my, um, my crazy attack yet.
DM: Oh, that's true. You can use your crazy attack.
Kenzo: Yeah. What the fuck, why not?
Kenzo: What are we here for? I'll do that.
Kenzo: I will, um,
Kenzo: I will use my staff to, uh,
Kenzo: do some crazy shit.
Kenzo: I get advantage now, right, because of you?
Wellby: Yes.
DM: Yes.
Kenzo: Awesome. All right, so I'm gonna do Vital Burst.
Kenzo: So now I get...
Kenzo: Until the beginning of my next turn, all attacks against me have disadvantage, my speed is doubled, and when I take the...
Kenzo: I get four attacks instead of two.
Kenzo: Well, that's perfect, 'cause now, 'cause we're 200 feet away, right?
DM: Yeah.
Kenzo: And I can fly.
DM: What's your move?
Kenzo: 70, but-
Unknown: It's doubled, so.
DM: So it's doubled, so 140.
Kenzo: But also, as an astral dude.
DM: I think that's just your speed.
Kenzo: [laughs] Okay.
Kenzo: Oh, that's all...
Unknown: So you can...
Kenzo: Oh, I can only...
Kenzo: Well, maybe I shouldn't use it now then, right?
Kenzo: Or can I get there in time?
Delwath: Well, you, you only if you use your bonus action.
DM: You could bonus action dash
DM: and get there and make four attacks with your staff.
Kenzo: Or otherwise I, otherwise I could just, I could save it for next round and then do seven attacks all at once.
DM: Well, but-
Delwath: But Wellby's advantage is gonna last only for this round.
Kenzo: Ah.
Unknown: You should, you should just-
Kenzo: Do it now
Delwath: ... you should do it now. Do four attacks with your staff with advantage.
Kenzo: Okay. All right.
Unknown: Yeah.
Kenzo: I'll do that.
DM: And if you want, um, well, probably no one else wants to get closer.
DM: If you're gonna use Step of the Wind-
Kenzo: Ah
DM: ... you can bring somebody with you.
Kenzo: You want to bring a leviathan?
Unknown: Sure.
Seeker: I'm the one that's trying to go straight in, so I should probably go first.
Kenzo: Bring, bring Seeker with you.
Unknown: Yeah.
Kenzo: All right. Wow.
Unknown: Amazing.
Kenzo: What a scene.
Kenzo: Okay, so-
Unknown: That's, that's weird. I like it.
Kenzo: Yeah, I Step of the Wind and I...
Kenzo: You're within five feet of me.
Kenzo: Oh, shit. I can bring a willing creature that is large or smaller.
Unknown: Wow.
DM: No, so you can't bring a leviathan.
Kenzo: That's bigger.
Unknown: That's a good point.
DM: A little bit too big to carry, even for a 20th level monk.
DM: [laughs]
Kenzo: That's a little... That would've been quite a sight, though.
Kenzo: Like-
DM: You can bring Wellby if he wants to get closer.
Kenzo: I don't think you do. Do you?
Wellby: I don't think so.
Unknown: No.
Kenzo: I don't think you do.
Unknown: Although-
Unknown: Does it matter?
Wellby: Not really at this point.
Kenzo: All right. I'll... All right, so now I guess I get up in-
Delwath: It has an acid... The other one had an acid goo shot.
Kenzo: Yeah.
Unknown: Being spread out is probably a good idea.
Unknown: Mm.
Kenzo: Yeah, spread out is good. Okay, and I will do four staff attacks with advantage.
Kenzo: Okay, let's see.
Unknown: Such a balance.
Seeker: Okay, so this is plus 15.
Unknown: 15.
Kenzo: All right, so first attack.
Kenzo: Oh, crit.
Unknown: One.
Unknown: Nice.
DM: Nice.
Kenzo: Okay.
Delwath: And you can do an extra D12, right?
DM: Yep.
Kenzo: Yeah. First attack.
DM: It's on your first attack, so you can-
Kenzo: Second attack, that definitely hits.
Kenzo: Third attack.
Kenzo: Ooh, 8, uh, 8 plus 15 is 23.
DM: That hits.
Kenzo: Third attack hits.
Kenzo: Fourth attack hits. Okay, so all four hit and I crit, so that's...
Unknown: So that's 4.
Unknown: That's, eh, 8.
Kenzo: No, no, no.
Unknown: 8D12.
Kenzo: 8D12?
Delwath: Yeah, 'cause you critted on the one that you get two D12s.
DM: You crit it on your first hit.
Kenzo: Yeah.
DM: Your first hit gives you two D12s.
Unknown: So that's four... Oh, no, seven.
Kenzo: 7D12.
Unknown: It's 7D12.
DM: [laughs] Oh, my God.
Unknown: 7D12 plus...
Unknown: Four attacks hit, so-
Kenzo: Plus, plus 9 times 4-
Unknown: Yeah
Kenzo: ... is 36.
Delwath: Yeah. So 7D12 plus 36.
Kenzo: Okay.
Kenzo: That's good. This is good.
Kenzo: D12s are so good.
Delwath: There's two right here. There's five right there.
Kenzo: Oops.
Kenzo: Five right here. Okay. All right.
Unknown: That's six.
Wellby: And here's 7.
Kenzo: Yeah. Oh, that's fun.
Kenzo: Okay, so 7D12 plus 36.
Seeker: Just roll it right on the, uh, on the ooze.
Kenzo: Yeah, I'll roll it on the ooze. [dice clatter] That is...
Kenzo: That's not-
Unknown: Reroll that.
Kenzo: Huh?
Unknown: Oh, one of them was on its side.
Kenzo: Oh, which one?
Unknown: That one.
Kenzo: Is it just-
Unknown: Just leave it.
Kenzo: I think it's fine.
Unknown: Just leave it, just leave it. It's fine.
Kenzo: 20, 35, uh,
Kenzo: 35. Oh, fuck. 35 plus 9 is 44.
Wellby: We're doomed.
Kenzo: 52 plus...
Unknown: 36.
Kenzo: 52 plus 36
Kenzo: is 88.
Wellby: That's 88.
Kenzo: 88.
Unknown: That's a lot.
Wellby: Holy shit. [laughs]
Kenzo: All right, 88.
Wellby: 88.
Kenzo: Cool.
DM: Okay, so you do 88 damage.
Unknown: Bam, bam, bam, bam.
DM: As four staff, four staff attacks all strike it.
DM: And as your, as your, um...
DM: Does that ends your turn?
Kenzo: Yes.
DM: As your turn ends-
Unknown: I'm moving pretty closer
Unknown: Same
DM: ... okay, um, the ooh- you see it moving stone out to the outside of the ooze.
DM: It hardens and protects itself.
Kenzo: From bludgeoning damage?
DM: It's, it switches resistance.
Kenzo: Yeah, yeah.
DM: So you just can't... So now it's not resistant to piercing, it is resistant to bludgeoning.
Kenzo: Oh, but I, I was doing... I can do force damage.
DM: Only with your punch, not with your staff.
Kenzo: No, I can do force damage with anything.
DM: Uh, when you make an unarmed strike you can switch it to force.
Kenzo: Okay, all right.
DM: Uh, but it doesn't matter, it just means you guys can't do the same damage type two rounds in a row.
Kenzo: Got it. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
DM: 'Cause it's reactive, not predictive.
Kenzo: Right.
Wellby: Does that make it complicated for the two of you?
Kenzo: Well, we just really only have bludgeoning damage-
DM: We only can
Seeker: ... for leviathan attacks, but I can cast spells.
Delwath: Right. And I'm... I actually think as soon as I get up to it, I'm just gonna change into Delwath.
DM: Uh, so that ended, uh, Kenza's turn.
Unknown: I don't know if that's a good idea, but.
DM: It's going to use, uh...
DM: So how... Wait, how close are the leviathans?
Unknown: 120.
Seeker: Yeah, we've done two 40 foot moves.
DM: Okay.
DM: Um, uh, it is going to, um...
DM: Oh, huh, this isn't gonna do anything, but it doesn't know that.
DM: Um, it's going to, um, uh, r- reach out, like with a, a s-, a pseudo, a spray of ooze, um, to hit Kenzo.
DM: Uh, that is...
DM: Oh, that's only a 20 to hit, so it misses
Kenzo: It does miss.
Unknown: Ooh.
Kenzo: I have an AC of 24 now.
DM: That's its legendary action.
Kenzo: Nice.
DM: Now it's its turn.
DM: Uh, it is going to-
Kenzo: Come at me, bro
DM: ... s-
DM: s- uh, move forward, attempting to engulf Kenzo.
Unknown: Oh.
DM: Make a strength saving throw.
Unknown: Well, that's new.
Kenzo: This one's got some different skills.
Unknown: The big one.
Kenzo: This one's got strength saving throw.
Unknown: Oh.
Kenzo: Uh-oh.
Kenzo: This is not good.
Delwath: Do our, um, breaths recharge?
Unknown: [die rolling] 20.
Kenzo: Oh.
DM: Oh my God.
Unknown: So you got a 19.
Kenzo: Huh?
DM: No, no, he's proficient.
Unknown: Ah.
DM: What's your total?
Kenzo: Huh? 20...
Kenzo: 25.
Unknown: 25.
DM: Okay, you succeed.
Kenzo: Oh, 'cause 20's not good enough anymore.
Unknown: Uh, you can't.
Kenzo: Oh.
Delwath: Saves don't have a crit success.
DM: Yeah, 20 doesn't automatically succeed on a save.
Delwath: Only, only attack rolls auto hit on a 20.
Kenzo: Wow. I think this is my first time ever making a strength save ever.
DM: [laughs]
Unknown: Probably. [laughs]
DM: Uh, so then it's gonna make two pseudopod attacks against you.
Kenzo: Kenzo, the true leviathan.
Unknown: Come at me. [die rolling]
DM: Uh, that's a natural one. That misses, and 28.
DM: That hits.
Kenzo: 28 hits.
DM: You take 24 points of force damage.
Unknown: Well, fuck you.
Kenzo: Um, no, yeah, no I don't.
Kenzo: I use my reaction.
DM: Okay.
Kenzo: Um, yeah, I automatically, uh, succeed.
DM: So Kenzo deflects.
Kenzo: Um, he has to roll a DC 20 dex.
Kenzo: [die rolling]
DM: Ah, that fails.
Kenzo: So it takes
Kenzo: 10, uh, it takes, uh, 17 more damage.
Kenzo: You try to hurt me instead of hurt yourself.
DM: Yep, so Kenzo ducks out of the way of two attacks.
Kenzo: Wait, it moved, it moved closer?
DM: It moved closer. It moved 30 feet closer.
Delwath: Okay. Wait, and I've moved twice, right?
Unknown: Yeah, we've moved
Unknown: 40 and 40 feet.
Kenzo: All right, guys. I've done 100, 100 damage.
Delwath: So 40, 40, plus 30, so it's 100.
DM: [coughs]
Unknown: So it's 80 feet away.
Kenzo: 80 away.
Unknown: I'm gonna use... Its turn's over?
DM: Uh, its turn is over, yes.
Unknown: I'm using n- my last legendary-
DM: Oh, wait, hold on
Delwath: ... to move 40 closer so I'm 50 feet away.
DM: No, no, nope. Sorry, I forgot its bonus action.
DM: Um-
Wellby: The, the clearing is like 400 feet across then?
DM: [coughs] Uh,
DM: uh, it's going to also, um,
DM: eject slime at
DM: Kenzo.
Kenzo: Wait, is this its turn or is its, uh, its bonus action?
DM: It's still its bonus action on its turn, yeah.
Unknown: On its turn, okay.
DM: Make a dex saving throw.
Kenzo: Come at me. [die rolling] What's that?
Unknown: Uh,
Unknown: 26.
DM: Okay. You dodged the slime.
Kenzo: Nice.
DM: [coughs] So evasion, so you take no damage.
Kenzo: Kenzo versus slime. Let's go.
DM: So that ends its turn.
DM: Delweth is up next.
DM: I'm gonna have to track its hit points on a spreadsheet because it's too complicated.
Seeker: You can take a legend- leg- your third legendary before your turn, right?
DM: Yes.
Delwath: Yes. So I'm moving 40 feet closer with my third legendary.
Delwath: So it moved 30 and I moved,
Delwath: uh, 40... 120, so it's 50 feet away right now.
Kenzo: Oh, we still can't close with it.
Delwath: Well, you can make your move.
Delwath: You're gonna be 10 feet away, so you can attack it but,
Unknown: um...
Unknown: Ooh, God, I can't decide what to do.
Kenzo: Um-
Seeker: It's resist- it's resistant to-
DM: Currently it's resistant to bludgeoning-
Unknown: Right
DM: ... and immune to acid and necrotic poison.
Delwath: It's like the leviathan can barely hurt it.
Seeker: So there's no other kind of damage you could do?
Unknown: I could turn into Delweth.
Kenzo: Hmm.
DM: This is a round with advantage.
Unknown: I'm really tempted to turn into Delweth.
Unknown: Ah, I'm gonna turn into Delweth.
Kenzo: Advantage is pretty great.
Delwath: I'm turning into Delweth.
Delwath: I'm 50 feet away. My speed is 60.
Delwath: Uh, my 10 pit points go away.
Kenzo: Oh.
Unknown: Um.
DM: Advantage would be awesome.
Delwath: And I'm gonna charge towards it as Delweth.
Unknown: Da, da, da, da, da.
Unknown: 50 feet move.
Unknown: I'll bonus action-
Kenzo: Crap
Delwath: ... I'll bonus action, um, um,
Delwath: explay, uh, Diaboli's Curse it.
DM: Okay.
Unknown: Um,
Delwath: uh, my weapon ignores resistance to slashing damage.
DM: Well, it's not currently resistant to slashing damage.
Unknown: I know. I'm just telling you.
DM: Yeah, I know.
Unknown: First attack.
DM: But you're the only one who does slashing damage-
Unknown: I know
DM: ... so it's never gonna be a problem for you.
Delwath: Uh, my first attack misses 'cause I can't roll above a five.
Kenzo: Ooh.
Unknown: I assume, uh,
Unknown: s- yeah, 17 misses.
DM: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Unknown: [die rolling] Second attack's better.
Delwath: That hits. [die rolling] And yeah.
Delwath: Third attack [die rolling] is much better.
Delwath: It crits. I'm gonna smite.
DM: Okay.
Kenzo: Nice. There we go.
DM: Yeah. Good move, good move.
Delwath: Um, so that is a total of one, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, 10, 11, 12 D6 from the smite-
Kenzo: What?
Delwath: ... plus, 'cause I critted on a smite.
Delwath: Um, so 66 plus my regular...
Delwath: Uh, 68 plus my regular two D8.
Delwath: Critted aga- man, so the smite, the smite attack alone does
Delwath: 16 D8. [laughs] Cr- critting on a smite is pretty bad.
DM: Yeah, it's pretty good.
Delwath: Okay, so that's 16 D8.
DM: It's a good thing I gave it a lot of hit points.
Delwath: Uh, and then my other attack that hit is two D8.
Delwath: So that is 18 D8.
DM: Whoo.
Kenzo: Wow. You rolling on your phone?
Unknown: Yeah.
Kenzo: Dodging.
Delwath: That's too many D... I'm not adding that up.
DM: Yeah.
Delwath: That, that's the worst damage roll I've ever seen in my life.
Delwath: 79 damage on 18 D8.
Unknown: That's awful.
DM: So Delweth runs forward.
Unknown: Plus, plus 10,
Delwath: plus 26... uh, plus 22.
DM: Still-
Delwath: So it's still 101
Unknown: Not bad
Wellby: Some, some
Seeker: Three, three digit damage on one attack
Wellby: Yeah, yeah
DM: Yeah, Delwath runs forward and slashes three times at it, appearing as himself.
DM: At the end of your turn, it is going to, um, use its last legendary for this round to shoot a glob of slime at you.
DM: Dexterity saving throw for Delwath.
Unknown: Uh, 18.
DM: That fails.
Unknown: Um,
Delwath: I have Bardak. I think Bardak's a better-
Wellby: Just do it. Make it restraint
Unknown: ... 'cause it was like a, a-
Wellby: A glob of slime or a net of slime?
DM: Um, this one looks like a glob of slime
Unknown: No, I'm using-
Wellby: This quest will restrain you anyways.
Unknown: Ah, no, it's 28.
DM: 28 succeeds. You dodge out of the way.
DM: Uh, oh, you do still take nine points of acid damage,
DM: and the glob retracts into its body.
Unknown: Ah, shit.
DM: Uh, that ends Delwath's turn.
DM: Um,
DM: did Seeker use all his legendary actions?
Unknown: I've only used two, so my turn-
DM: So you can do one right before your turn.
DM: Your turn is next
Seeker: Yeah, my, my turn takes me another 40,
Unknown: so I'm also
Unknown: 10 feet away from it now, I think.
DM: Yep.
Unknown: Yeah.
Unknown: So I'm right up close.
Unknown: I could now
Unknown: either
Seeker: go for incapacitating it with Rune of Psychic Destruction
Unknown: and save or-
Delwath: It's a bump damage. It's above average.
Wellby: It wasn't as bad as I thought
Seeker: ... or I could try to dash and just, like, dive into the center of it.
DM: Oh, wait. Sorry, Mike. You did slashing damage to it, right?
Unknown: Slashing, yeah.
DM: Um, acid erupts in the wound.
DM: You take six points of acid damage.
DM: The first time you hit it each round,
DM: I'll roll differently
Unknown: Okay.
Delwath: Uh, is that, uh...
Unknown: I'm 10 feet away.
DM: Yeah, you're within 60 feet-
Unknown: Okay
DM: ... so the acid spray still hits it.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: Do what?
Seeker: I was thinking about trying to i- incapacitate it with Rune of Psychic Destruction-
DM: Yeah
Seeker: ... versus just dash and, like, dive.
DM: Just don't waste a high level spell slot while it still has all its legendary resistances.
Wellby: Oh, right.
Unknown: Right, so I-
DM: It's a good thing to try and force it to save, 'cause it's bad at end
Unknown: Yeah. Mm.
Seeker: So, so I shouldn't just di- dive for this as well?
DM: No, I'm just saying don't, like, burn your eighth level slot on a Rune of Psychic Destruction-
Unknown: Yeah
DM: ... when it's going to use a legendary if it fails.
Unknown: So I can use a much lower...
Seeker: I can use a fourth level on Psychic Destruction
DM: It's a strong effect, 'cause if it fails the save, it's gotta burn a legendary resistance.
DM: Being incapacitated is really bad.
Kenzo: All right. So yeah, I will do the Psychic Destruction.
Wellby: Nice. It's immune to exhaustion
DM: It's immune to exhaustion
Unknown: And to save, you can empty.
DM: Uh,
DM: it burns a legendary resistance.
Wellby: Nice.
Seeker: Nice. And then I can use my move still to go onto it, right?
DM: Yep.
Unknown: On the ooze.
DM: Okay.
Unknown: And then-
DM: That ends Seeker's turn. Wellby is up.
Wellby: Uh, oh
DM: Sorry, actually, one sec.
DM: So-
Seeker: I was gonna maybe do the concert idea. Let me do it next.
Wellby: Next turn, yeah
DM: So at the start of the round,
DM: I'm gonna do a little recap at the beginning of each round.
DM: It's 'cause it's hard to track with the battle map not being perfect.
DM: So Wellby is still 180 feet away, or 170 feet away from it on the edge of the battlefield, aiming with his bow, while Kenzo has just dodged
DM: out of the way of its attempt to engulf him.
DM: Delwath is on the other side of the front, 10 feet away from it, and Seeker has just dived towards the middle of the goop.
DM: And we will see what happens.
DM: [laughs]
Wellby: It's probably be fine. It's not, uh, it's not, uh, resistant to piercing anymore, right?
DM: Nope. It's now resis- it's currently still resistant to sl-
Wellby: Slashing
DM: ... slashing 'cause that's the last damage it took.
Wellby: Oh. Yeah.
Wellby: Yeah. Okay. So I will shoot it.
Kenzo: So what's the thing where you shoot it and then we get advantage?
Unknown: Why, what, what
DM: That's only the first round
Unknown: What effect does that have?
DM: It's a rogue s- it's a scout rogue ability.
Wellby: Uh, Second Strike or something like that.
Unknown: Yeah. That's awesome.
Unknown: I love having advantage.
Wellby: Uh, 20-
Unknown: I know
Wellby: ... 3 at least.
DM: 23 hits, yes.
Wellby: Uh, all right. And all the damage is...
Wellby: [dice rolling] Uh, okay.
Wellby: 10, 15, 29, 32, 40.
Wellby: 40.
DM: 40 piercing?
Wellby: Yep.
DM: Uh, so as you expect, as the arrow hits, it, um...
DM: Oh, sorry, that's gonna be at the end of your turn.
Wellby: With the advantage, yeah [laughs]
DM: If you want to do another attack, it won't be resistant to it
Wellby: Another attack.
Wellby: Uh, something like 30.
Wellby: [die rolling] Uh, another 12 points of piercing.
Wellby: Yeah.
DM: Okay.
Wellby: That's me.
DM: Um, it is going to use, at the end of your turn, it's going to use a legendary resistance.
DM: I mean, a legendary... Well, first it's...
DM: Sorry, not a legendary resistance. It again becomes this sort of gloopy mess, resistant to piercing.
DM: It's gonna use a legendary action
DM: to, let's see, use that one.
DM: Uh,
DM: it will try that one on...
DM: You're out of range, so it'll try that on Delwath.
DM: Um, it reaches out to hit you.
DM: [die rolling] 60 foot reach.
DM: Uh,
DM: whoops, I didn't mean to roll advantage, but a 24.
Unknown: That's shield.
DM: Okay.
DM: So that misses. That's its legendary action.
DM: Uh, Kenzo is up.
Unknown: All right.
Unknown: Kenzo is gonna-
Wellby: Oh, can I...
DM: You can legendary action
Seeker: Yeah, go, do it. I'm just g- so should I bludgeon...
Unknown: Should I slam attack or should I just...
Unknown: No, I should probably-
DM: No
Seeker: ... attack it so it doesn't attack me and then just use-
DM: No, but don't bludgeon because then-
Unknown: Right, but that can't, yeah
DM: ... it'll be resistant to Kenzo's attacks.
Seeker: So with my move, can I try to, like, tunnel into it?
Unknown: Sure
Unknown: Right?
Delwath: I mean, well, if I think and move up to move through other creatures and up the space of one inch.
DM: Make a s- make a strength check.
Unknown: Yeah.
Unknown: Well, if I think-
DM: Or athle- well, yeah.
Unknown: No, it's-
DM: Athletics, but it's just straight strength
Unknown: 27 strength.
Unknown: Plus eight.
Unknown: [dice rolling] That's a 21.
DM: Um, you, you push your way through it a little bit.
Unknown: [squelching]
DM: Like,
DM: it's, it's currently a little bit gloopy 'cause it's, like, thinned itself out to be resistant to piercing damage.
Unknown: Amazing.
DM: So you-
Unknown: So how are you doing it [laughs]?
DM: You tunnel 40 feet in, so you're-
Unknown: Well, am I swimming in the ooze?
Unknown: 'Cause that's [laughs] only 20 foot.
DM: Mm.
Unknown: [laughs]
DM: I'll say it's swimming, but it counts as difficult terrain, so you can move 60 feet.
Seeker: Amazing. I'm going straight down.
DM: So you, you still have 100...
DM: You still have 200 feet, or 200 feet of ooze to cross before you even get to the part that goes down.
Unknown: Oh, okay. So-
DM: So you're 140 feet from the sinkhole.
Delwath: So you're about... And the sinkhole is, like, 40 feet we think, or 30 feet.
DM: The sinkhole is, like, 40 feet deep.
Delwath: So you're, you're 160 feet from it.
Unknown: [laughs]
Kenzo: No, you know what, though? You know what, though?
Unknown: Come with me, guys.
Kenzo: No, but if he gets, like, to where we need to go-
Unknown: [laughs]
Kenzo: ... I wonder if he can dimension door or just teleport us right to the, the, you know.
Unknown: That's insane.
Kenzo: Like, you know what I'm saying? Like, once you get there.
Wellby: Well, you can keep moving with your other legendary actions.
Unknown: Yeah, yeah, keep go. Next action.
DM: Yeah, it's Kenzo's turn now.
Unknown: Yeah.
Kenzo: Yeah.
Kenzo: But keep going in there.
Unknown: [laughs]
Kenzo: Let's see what's-
Unknown: Just, just go for it
Kenzo: ... yeah, let's see what's at the heart of this thing.
Unknown: [laughs]
Kenzo: This is cool. I like this.
Kenzo: This is, this is, this is
Kenzo: really weird and awesome.
Unknown: Yeah. This, this leviathan thing is really cool.
Kenzo: Yeah, the leviathan tunneling into the middle of the ooze.
DM: Seeker much prefers to be a leviathan [laughs] than a dragon.
Kenzo: Yeah.
Delwath: I mean, it helps to pick something that's immune to the primary damage type.
Kenzo: Yeah. Yeah.
Delwath: But it's throwing force now. You will take the force damage.
Kenzo: Um.
Unknown: Oh, okay.
Delwath: But, again, unless you take 22, you can't fail the...
Unknown: Yeah.
Kenzo: Okay. So I'm gonna-
Unknown: I'll s- like, attack the body
Kenzo: ... attack a lot. I don't have advantage anymore, right?
DM: You don't have advantage anymore, no.
Kenzo: Okay. First staff attack, uh, 24 hits.
DM: Yep.
Kenzo: Actually, I'll do these all together.
Unknown: Yeah.
Kenzo: Uh.
Delwath: No, just roll the staff attack and then roll the-
Kenzo: Yeah. The second staff attack. Oh, great.
Unknown: Nice.
Kenzo: Holy shit.
DM: Good job.
Kenzo: Great. And then, um, three unarmed strikes.
Kenzo: Here.
Kenzo: Um, [dice rolling] uh, plus 13, so-
Unknown: 19 will miss.
DM: 19 misses. And-
Kenzo: Everything else hits
Unknown: So it's 20.
Kenzo: 22 hits.
Unknown: 22 hits.
DM: 22 hits.
Kenzo: Yeah. Yeah. Okay. So,
Kenzo: oh, fuck. How do we calculate this?
Delwath: Is it your first attack?
DM: The, the first attack that hits.
DM: The, you can't... Yeah.
Unknown: Yeah, it's the first attack that hits.
DM: Yeah.
Delwath: So it's, uh, 2d, it's 4d 12,
Delwath: plus two more, so 6d 12.
DM: 6d 12 plus...
Unknown: 6d 12 plus-
DM: Plus 18 plus 14
Kenzo: 18 plus 14, yeah.
DM: Yeah. [laughs] Jesus. Okay.
DM: Well, I'm calculating this with a spreadsheet, so 18, 14, just tell me what the 6d 12 are.
Kenzo: Okay. So 6d 1, 2, 3, 4...
Kenzo: Wait, is somewhere.
DM: Yeah, that should be 20. That's a 12.
Kenzo: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Kenzo: [dice rolling] Okay. If, uh...
Kenzo: Oh, this is noth- oh, this is terrible.
DM: That's a terrible roll.
Kenzo: Yeah.
Kenzo: 10, 20, 24.
DM: Okay.
Kenzo: 24 plus-
DM: Yep
Kenzo: ... how much?
DM: I got it. I got it. 24 plus 18 plus 14.
Kenzo: Okay.
DM: I just, I just have a spreadsheet-
Kenzo: Yeah, yeah
DM: ... that's subtracting its hit points-
DM: ... 'cause it's too complicated in here. Ah, Seeker, from inside you feel as it hardens to stone, this, like, to be resistant to bludgeoning damage, this m- this, like, tight
DM: mesh kind of traps itself around you.
Kenzo: Ugh.
Seeker: Am I... Can I use my legendary action to keep him in the ooze?
Unknown: [laughs]
DM: Uh.
Unknown: [coughs]
DM: Y- you can try. But first it gets to use its last legendary action for this round.
Unknown: Mm.
DM: Um, sorry, for its, its round one.
Delwath: You should be able to, like, try and punch through with your-
Unknown: Yeah
Unknown: ... super strength.
Unknown: Leviathan strength.
DM: Uh, it's...
DM: Yes. It's just, it's easier to move through depending on what it's resistant to.
Unknown: Yeah, yeah, yeah. It, yeah.
DM: Um, so it's gonna use its legendary first,
DM: um, and it is going to, uh,
DM: try
DM: the
DM: corrupting touch on Kenzo again.
DM: [dice rolling]
Unknown: That's total crap.
DM: That's a 30-something to hit.
Unknown: Okay, that hits.
DM: Um, you take-
Unknown: I'm fine. You can't be corrupted
DM: ... 23 points of poison damage.
Unknown: I have?
Unknown: No you don't
DM: ... whi- which you're resistant to.
Unknown: I-
DM: And you are poisoned, which you are immune to, so it does nothing to you.
Kenzo: Well, but also 23, I'm gonna use my reaction.
Unknown: 23.
Unknown: And, um, I should be good.
DM: Yeah, you just got reaction back.
DM: So you take no damage.
DM: It's really not doing well attacking Kenzo.
Kenzo: With a DC 20. [dice rolling]
DM: It, uh, that it passed.
Unknown: Okay.
DM: So now it's Seeker legendary action.
Seeker: I will try to fight through, keep moving.
DM: Strength, strength check.
DM: Higher DC this time. [dice rolling]
Kenzo: Nice.
Unknown: So that's a 22.
DM: A 22? Okay.
DM: You push your way through.
Unknown: Leviathan.
DM: Uh, this...
Unknown: [laughs]
DM: Yeah. I, um, this is, like, twice difficult terrain now, so you move 30 feet.
Unknown: 30, okay.
DM: You need to get back to piercing.
DM: That's the easiest to swim through.
DM: Uh-
Unknown: I, I'll let you know [laughs]
DM: ... now it's its turn.
Unknown: Piercing, piercing.
DM: It is going to move forward and attempt to engulf Kenzo and Delwath.
Unknown: Oh, no.
DM: Strength saves from both of you.
Unknown: Oh no, I hate this.
Unknown: [laughs]
Unknown: I hate this.
Delwath: Well, I have ways to get out of this once we-
Seeker: I, I engulfed myself, guys. It's not so bad.
DM: Uh-
Unknown: I hate this. Yeah
DM: ... your turn hasn't started yet, Del, since you dived into it.
Unknown: Oh, 21.
Unknown: What's that? No, I'm just saying, they're tr-
Unknown: Three
Seeker: ... he's, it's trying to engulf them. I'm like, that's-
DM: Uh, both of those fail.
Unknown: Uh, I will re-roll.
DM: Okay.
Unknown: Spend a ki to try to re-roll.
Kenzo: Fuck, I need to get even higher than a 16.
Unknown: Shit.
DM: Uh, you are... Delwath is engulfed.
DM: [dice rolling]
Unknown: What does being engulfed mean?
Unknown: 15.
Unknown: 15 is what I was-
Unknown: 20.
Unknown: 16.
DM: You are also engulfed.
Unknown: Oh, no.
DM: You are, you have total cover from attacks and other effects outside the ooze, and it moves you with it, and then you'll see what else happen.
DM: Oh, and you're- Suffocating and restrained
Unknown: Oh, God. What does that mean?
DM: Disadvantage on all attacks
Seeker: And you can see Leviathan swimming inside the ooze
DM: Uh,
DM: and that ends its turn. Delwath is up.
DM: Uh, you take-
Wellby: Leviathan
Kenzo: Wait, can I be res- can I be res- restrained as a, as a natural being?
DM: Yeah.
Unknown: Can-
DM: It doesn't say you're immune to restraint
Kenzo: I can pass through objects and creatures, except barriers of magical force, as if they were difficult terrain
DM: Uh, Delwath takes 22 points of force damage.
Delwath: Okay. Hold on one second. I'm just trying to look at one thing.
Delwath: Um, okay, 22 points of force damage and I...
Delwath: Wait, I have disadvantage on attacks?
DM: Yep
Unknown: Um,
Unknown: uh,
Unknown: okay. But
Delwath: I turn into a cloud immune to restraint.
DM: Yep
Delwath: Okay. So I use a metamagic to bonus action
Delwath: transform. Delwath transforms into, like, a cloud of, like,
Delwath: some kind of, like, maybe like a water creature of some...
Delwath: A little water insect of some kind.
Unknown: Uh, which, um-
Seeker: You turn into a tiny cloud of tiny bugs
Delwath: A cloud of tiny bugs. You've seen Delwath do this before
Unknown: Mm-hmm
Delwath: ... uh, which is immune to restraint, so I presumably no longer restrained.
DM: Yep
Delwath: And then I can move to the outside of it.
DM: Uh, yep.
Unknown: Okay. So I...
Unknown: That's my bonus action.
Delwath: Now I'm outside it and I will attack it.
Unknown: I'll be 20 feet away.
Unknown: Uh, oh, wait, how much damage did you say?
Unknown: 22?
DM: 22 points of force.
Unknown: Uh, 24
DM: Uh, 24 hits.
Unknown: Uh,
Unknown: 22
DM: That hits
Unknown: And higher than either of those.
Delwath: Uh, one, two, three, four, five, six.
Delwath: So that is 32 damage plus
Unknown: 15 plus 18.
DM: 32 plus 15 plus 18?
Unknown: Yep. Three attacks.
Unknown: I used my bonus action.
Delwath: I used a quicken metamagic-
DM: So that ends-
Unknown: ... which costs me a lot
DM: Oh, wait. Sorry, I forgot.
DM: It was bonus action.
DM: Um,
DM: uh, I'm gonna-
Unknown: Um
DM: ... just run it as a legendary.
Delwath: I'm gonna smite it also
DM: Okay
Wellby: Do Tasha's Hideous Laughter incapacitates?
Unknown: I mean, I have wish.
Unknown: That's 30 more damage.
DM: Okay
Unknown: Is that 100?
DM: Uh, so it also-
Wellby: But it incapacitates
DM: Uh-
Unknown: I see.
Seeker: Yeah, th- that's what I was going for with second
DM: Sleep also incapacitates
Wellby: Sleep still work with the hit die or no?
Unknown: Nah, it's... Now it's just an incapacitate save
DM: So, um, Wellby, make a dexterity saving throw.
Unknown: So I need to use my bonus action-
DM: As another glob of acid flies towards you
Unknown: ... to escape on this turn.
Unknown: But if I-
Wellby: Uh, uh, 20
DM: Fails
Wellby: Huh. [laughs]
DM: You want to do something? Do you have anything you can do?
Wellby: I... No, I've burned the heroic. I've burned the bardic.
DM: Okay.
DM: Uh, you take...
DM: Ooh, why isn't that working? Uh,
DM: I'm gonna have to roll this manually.
DM: Sorry, 10 D10 takes a while.
DM: Uh, you take 10, 19-
Unknown: Oh
DM: ...
DM: uh,
DM: 29, 31
DM: plus seven-
Wellby: That's lovely
DM: ... so 40.
DM: 57 points of acid damage.
Wellby: Is this a uncanny dodge sort of a thing?
DM: No, it's a saving throw
Wellby: All right
DM: And you are dragged, uh,
DM: 60 feet closer towards the ooze.
Wellby: Awesome
DM: So you are now-
Wellby: 110
DM: ... 110 feet away.
DM: Uh, no, it moved 30 feet on its turn, so you're now-
Unknown: 80
DM: ... 80 feet away.
Wellby: Got it.
DM: Um, and it is now gonna use...
DM: That was actually a bonus action on its turn, which I forgot.
DM: So after Delwath's turn, it's using a legendary action to crush those inside it.
Seeker: Oh no, me and Kenza.
DM: [laughs]
Wellby: Good
DM: Uh, make a strength saving throw.
Wellby: Tim, I'm pulled closer but not grappled or restrained
DM: But not grappled or restrained, no
Wellby: So it's fine
Unknown: That's, uh, 23.
Unknown: 23.
Unknown: Sure.
DM: Uh,
DM: both of you rolled a 23?
Unknown: No, you rolled a 23. I have a-
DM: Oh, 23 succeeds
Unknown: Something really high.
Unknown: Uh, it's not high enough. 17.
DM: 17-
Unknown: I'm, I'm gonna reroll
DM: Okay.
Unknown: Uh, it didn't help
DM: So 17 fails, so, um...
DM: Ugh, why isn't this dice roller working?
DM: Okay. Uh,
DM: Kenza takes 31 points of force damage.
DM: Um, you take half that.
Unknown: So-
DM: So 15
Unknown: ...
Unknown: 15.
DM: Uh, and that's its legendary, so Seeker is up.
Unknown: Ugh.
Unknown: Down to 306. [laughs]
Unknown: Plus Seeker hit points
Seeker: Yeah. [laughs] Well, it would be bad to be back to Seeker.
Unknown: I'd be inside the ooze, so.
Unknown: True
Unknown: Um,
Unknown: oh, I can use my...
Unknown: Crap, do I have another legendary?
Unknown: I think I do.
Unknown: I think I used two already.
Unknown: Yeah
DM: You used two, so you can use one more-
Unknown: At the, at the-
DM: ... at the end of Delwath's
Unknown: ...
Delwath: move, move towards it. Move inside it, right?
Seeker: Yeah, I keep moving as much as possible
DM: Okay, so another strength check.
Seeker: How far away is this, this...
Unknown: Oh
Unknown: ... natural one
DM: You do not move any further
Wellby: All right
Seeker: Okay. And then on my turn...
Unknown: How many... It's burned one legendary?
DM: You've burned one legendary resistance, yeah
Kenzo: Yeah, make it do some other unsavvy things
Unknown: Versus just trying to move a lot more
DM: And wait, Dal- you were the last one to attack it.
Unknown: Yes, I did.
DM: So it's currently immune to slashing.
Unknown: Currently what?
DM: Immune to slashing, or resistant to slashing.
Unknown: Hmm.
Unknown: There's some other stuff it could use.
DM: I mean-
Seeker: No, I'll just, I'll just do psychic disruption again.
DM: Okay.
Unknown: Uh, so yeah.
DM: That fails again.
Unknown: Fourth one.
DM: Oh wait, it hasn't been.
DM: Uh, oh no, that's gonna succeed.
Unknown: No.
DM: 21.
DM: Wait, 21. What's your d...
DM: It's-
Unknown: 19.
DM: Okay, so it succeeds.
Unknown: Yeah. Dope.
Delwath: So you can still use your move to move.
Seeker: Yes, I use my move to move.
DM: Yeah. So another strength check.
Unknown: 16.
DM: Yeah, that's fine.
Delwath: So you move 60 further?
DM: 60 further, yeah.
Unknown: Okay.
Unknown: So now on the track.
Unknown: You should just write down on the-
DM: Just keep track on the...
DM: You, I think you were a hundred and tw-
Delwath: You were a hundred and... You were, you were-
DM: You had moved 90 feet.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: So you move another... You moved 150 feet.
Unknown: [gasps]
DM: So you're 50 feet from the sinkhole now.
Unknown: Right.
Unknown: Okay.
DM: Um, that ends Seeker's turn.
DM: It will use another legendary resistance.
DM: It already did the-
Unknown: Action
DM: ... sorry, action. It already did the force crush.
DM: Uh,
DM: Delwath is just standing outside there.
DM: It's gonna pseudopod hit you.
DM: That's a 30.
Unknown: Okay.
DM: Uh, that is going to be 21 points of force damage.
DM: Um,
DM: Wellby is up, so as the round begins, now Kenzo is being slowly crushed inside the blob.
DM: Seeker is-
Unknown: Charging
DM: ... charging through the blob.
DM: Um,
DM: Wellby is-
Wellby: Wellby moves back to I think 170 is now the furthest distance away-
DM: Okay
Wellby: ... that I can get. And shoots.
Unknown: Nice.
Unknown: Safety first, Wellby.
Unknown: Yeah. Safety first indeed.
DM: Mm-hmm.
Unknown: Uh, that's a hit.
Delwath: Wait, what did we... We know its AC is 22, right?
Unknown: Or at least not higher than 22.
Unknown: 22.
DM: Not higher than 22. A 22 hits.
Unknown: Okay.
DM: A 20... I don't think anybody's rolled a 21.
Unknown: Mm-hmm.
DM: A 20 misses.
Unknown: Okay. For 42.
DM: 42 piercing?
Unknown: Yep. Second attack,
Unknown: uh, also hits.
Unknown: Uh, nine piercing.
Kenzo: Piercing plus b- Pushen's bonus, I guess.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: Yep.
DM: Uh, that ends Wellby's turn. It will use its last legendary action for this round
DM: to,
DM: uh-
Unknown: Wait, isn't this the beginning of-
DM: Its legend is reset-
Unknown: On its turn
DM: ... on, on its turn.
Unknown: Oh, yeah, yeah.
DM: Um, it is going to,
DM: uh...
DM: It did crush, it did pseudopod.
DM: It's gonna... Uh, how far did you s- you were 170 away?
Unknown: Uh, feet, yeah.
DM: Okay. It can't reach you, so it's gonna shoot at Delwath.
Unknown: My strategy's working.
DM: Uh, dex saving throw.
DM: Wait, how long does the butterflies last?
Unknown: Oh, it lasts till the, till...
Unknown: It lasts for, for-
DM: Just for your turn?
Unknown: I think it lasts for just my turn.
DM: So are you current... You're not currently immune to restraint, are you?
Unknown: Not anymore.
DM: Okay. What is your dex save?
Delwath: Uh, six, but plus something, but it's not gonna succeed.
DM: Okay. Uh-
Unknown: It might...
Unknown: Heroic.
Unknown: Yeah.
Unknown: You don't want to be restrained.
Delwath: I mean, I can get out again, but it's annoying.
Unknown: Yeah.
Unknown: Dope.
DM: Uh, you take 16 points of acid damage, and it
DM: sucks you into itself.
DM: So you're engulfed again.
Delwath: [laughs] Delwath just kind of frowns at it, like, "Wait a minute."
DM: Uh, Kenzo's up.
Seeker: Oh, and I'll move again.
DM: Uh, yes. So now it's easy DC and you can move 60 feet 'cause it's resistant to piercing.
Unknown: Do I have to roll?
DM: No, you still have to roll, but it's easy.
Unknown: That's a 24.
DM: Yeah, that succeeds.
Seeker: So now I'm at the sinkhole 'cause I was 50 away, and then I can move 10 more straight down.
DM: Yep.
DM: So you're now 30 feet away from the
DM: top. 10, 19.
Seeker: It's 30 away from the thing.
DM: 25. From, sorry, from the bottom.
Unknown: Okay. There.
DM: 25, 28. Kenzo, at the start of your turn you take 28 points of force damage.
Unknown: What?
Unknown: 28?
DM: Yep.
Unknown: So how far, uh-
DM: Oh, wait. Sorry, Eric, did I...
DM: At the start of your turn, did I tell you how much force damage you took?
Unknown: No.
Unknown: Didn't I roll a save?
DM: That was the first legendary action.
Unknown: Right.
DM: You also take force damage if you start your turn inside it.
Unknown: Oh, okay. Okay. No, yeah.
DM: Uh, okay. So 22 for you.
Unknown: 22.
Unknown: Down below 300, guys.
DM: That's rough.
Unknown: [laughs]
DM: Okay.
Delwath: Delwath's kind of questioning his life choices that led him to not being a leviathan.
Unknown: [laughs]
DM: [laughs]
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: Leviathan.
Unknown: How many, um-
DM: Oh, wait, sorry. You're immune to the restrained condition, so that's why you didn't take force damage.
DM: It can only do force damage to you if it intentionally squeezes.
DM: You don't take force damage just from being inside.
Unknown: Oh. Yeah. So add them back.
DM: 'Cause you're immune to restraint.
Unknown: So I add 22 back? Yeah.
DM: Yeah.
Kenzo: How many feet am I away from, like, escaping?
Unknown: Oh, it can work.
DM: Ah.
Unknown: That's fine.
Unknown: 'Cause it engulfed me.
DM: So you're, you're still-
Unknown: It's not important though. We probably just have to edit it to 284-
DM: Uh, you're still like, you're restrained.
DM: You need to, you need to make the strength saving throw to be unrestrained before you can escape.
Kenzo: I need to make a strength sp- saving throw?
Kenzo: Even, even if I'm a, if, uh, an astral construct?
DM: Yeah. It has like, it's a n- like network of this stuff that's like grappled around you.
DM: Um, the ghostly form does not make you immune to the restraint.
DM: I mean, it... Things can still stop your movement and you're restrained.
Kenzo: And I'm a... Is this, is it, is it just a regular strength save or is it at disadvantage?
DM: No, just reg- it's a strength save.
DM: You don't have disadvantage on str- 'cause you just need to, you just need to break through this, these filaments and then you can-
Unknown: Yeah
DM: ... s- fly out because of your, um-
Kenzo: I- is it, uh... Also, is it the case that, um,
Kenzo: um, to try to escape, is that a bose- bonus action to move or is it something I could just, I just try?
DM: You just automatically get a strength save at the end of every turn to, like, bust the-
Kenzo: But it's at the end of the turn?
DM: It's at the end of your turn.
Kenzo: Okay.
DM: I mean, you could, if you wanted to use your action to attempt to escape, you could also use your action to make a strength save.
Kenzo: So, so I could do twice?
DM: You could do it twice, but you use your whole action if you do that.
DM: It's-
Kenzo: Well, but I mean, I'm stuck here right now.
DM: Well, you could, you could still attack it.
Kenzo: You can attack with it
DM: ... you're inside.
Kenzo: Yeah, but that's, that's not... 'Cause I'm also getting crushed every round that I'm in here.
DM: Yes.
Kenzo: The only, the only type of damage that I'm not resistant to is force damage.
DM: Mm-hmm.
Kenzo: So this is like not a good place for me to be.
Kenzo: Okay, uh, I'm gonna bonus action, um, drink the potion of speed just-
DM: Okay
Kenzo: ... 'cause why the fuck not?
Kenzo: Um, so now-
Delwath: Oh, 'cause then you could do one attack
Kenzo: ... bonus action.
Wellby: Yeah. Or you could try and-
Kenzo: I can try, I can try to escape three times.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: No. C- the hasted action can, can only be used for a few limited things, right?
Delwath: But, but utilize is one of them.
Unknown: I would argue that counts.
DM: Yeah, that probably d- Let me just look at haste for one sec.
DM: Yeah, yeah, yeah. It would be like equivalent to basically taking the dash action.
DM: So yeah, you can make three attempts.
Kenzo: Okay, great. This is kind of six attempts because-
Unknown: Seven
Kenzo: ... each, each one that I fail I can try to reroute and spend a ki if I want.
Delwath: But do use your hasted attempt first.
Kenzo: Okay.
Wellby: 'Cause you can't use it for other-
Kenzo: Well, no, no. But I should use my, my just-
Unknown: Because it... No, no, no.
Delwath: Use your h- you... That's a... Yeah, use your haste one first because then if you succeed you can use your regular action to attack three times.
Kenzo: Ah.
DM: Yeah.
Unknown: Right?
Wellby: I see what you're saying.
Delwath: But if the regular one succeeds you can only attack once with haste.
Kenzo: Okay, got it. But I can't use that, 'cause the, the...
Kenzo: I also just like... Oh, but that's at the end of my turn.
Unknown: That's the end of your turn.
Kenzo: Got it. Okay. All right.
Unknown: Your free one's at the end of your turn.
Kenzo: Fucking bitch.
Wellby: Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Kenzo: All right. First one.
Kenzo: Damn it, 16. That fails.
DM: Fails.
Kenzo: I'm gonna spend a ki to retry that one.
Kenzo: Ah, fucking bitch.
Kenzo: Yes.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: 25-
Unknown: Good retry
DM: ... does succeed.
Kenzo: Thank fucking God. Oh my God, that was pretty stressful.
Kenzo: All right.
Wellby: That's the third 20 you've rolled in this combat.
DM: Yeah.
Unknown: Wow.
Kenzo: Yeah. But, um, two of them have been for saves which has been kind of useful.
Kenzo: That's, it's just two successes.
Delwath: So, sorry, which a- That was your hasted action?
DM: Okay.
Kenzo: That was my hasted action. Okay, so now I get three attacks.
Unknown: Now you can break free if you want.
DM: So you're not as, you're not restrained now, so you can fly out of it with your astral being.
Kenzo: Right.
Unknown: So move.
Kenzo: I will move. I will move the full 70 feet.
Kenzo: The thing is, I do not want it to do that shit again, 'cause every time it does that, like strength saves are fucking terrible.
Kenzo: I cannot... I, I feel like I need to, like-
Delwath: But remember that you're hasted
Kenzo: ... I just know that if I succeed-
Delwath: Its range is 60 feet, so it's tough.
Delwath: Oh, what you, what you need to do is attack it and then-
Kenzo: And then move
Delwath: ... and then move after your attack.
Kenzo: Yeah.
Unknown: You w-
Kenzo: That's exactly what I'm gonna do.
Delwath: Oh, no. Wait, haste doubles your speed?
Kenzo: It does.
DM: Yeah.
Kenzo: So I've got 140 move now.
Unknown: So yeah, do that.
Kenzo: Totally.
Unknown: Fly out of it.
Kenzo: I already-
Delwath: On your way out... [imitates clashing]
Kenzo: Yeah, on my way out I hit it three times-
Unknown: And then keep going
Kenzo: ... and then I'll, and then I keep going.
Delwath: You might get an opportunity attack against you, but it-
DM: You hit it twice.
Kenzo: Huh?
Unknown: Twice.
DM: Twice with your-
Delwath: Not th- Yeah, sorry. Yeah, 'cause you don't have your bonus action, so twice.
Unknown: Two staff attacks.
Kenzo: Just because I drank a potion.
DM: You drank your potion and then-
Kenzo: All right, so-
DM: Yeah.
Kenzo: All right. So I get two att- staff attacks.
Unknown: Yes.
Kenzo: Just regular-
Unknown: Yes
Kenzo: ... normal staff attacks. All right, cool.
Kenzo: And they both... 21.
Kenzo: Does 21 hit?
DM: 21 does not hit.
Unknown: Dope.
Kenzo: All right, so only one hits.
Kenzo: One attack.
Unknown: Was that a six and a nine?
Kenzo: Yeah, six and a nine. I have a plus 15.
Unknown: Oh, the 21.
Unknown: Sorry, you were doing the higher one.
Kenzo: Yeah. Yeah. Well, no, this is, this is two attacks.
Unknown: Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Kenzo: All right. So I get, uh-
Unknown: I was doing the math wrong. I thought-
Kenzo: You get two, d-
Unknown: I thought the six was the 20
Kenzo: ... two D12, two D12 plus nine.
Delwath: No, a nine, a nine plus...
Unknown: Don't you have a plus 15?
DM: So one of the two attacks hit.
DM: The 21 misses.
Unknown: Ah. Oh, oh. Yeah, yeah.
DM: So if the 21-
Unknown: Sorry, I thought you said they both hit
DM: ... but you know that 21, that 22 hits.
Unknown: Yeah, yeah.
DM: So now you know its AC is 21.
Kenzo: All right. So that's 14 plus 9 is 23, and I move 140.
Kenzo: Get the fuck out of there. Oh, wait, no, I don't want to move all full.
Kenzo: What's the, what's the extent of its attack?
Unknown: We don't know. It could be 600 feet.
DM: It's been hitting Wellby from 600 feet away.
Kenzo: God.
Wellby: Even shoots the-
Kenzo: But, but, but no, but this, the engulf is 60 foot, right?
DM: Oh, the engulf was, well, 60 f- maybe.
DM: You don't quite know for sure.
Kenzo: Because the thing is, if I move 140, then I'd have to, like, just fly back in to attack it, and then I would be stuck right next to it.
Unknown: You should be... I would be...
Delwath: You can move 140 a turn.
Kenzo: Yeah.
Delwath: So if you're 70 feet away from it-
Kenzo: Yeah
Delwath: ... you can fly in and fly out in the same turn.
Kenzo: All right. I'll, I'll go, I'll go to 70 feet away and hope that that is, you know, a good distance.
DM: Okay. It is its turn now, um, relentlessly moving towards the three people here.
Kenzo: Oh, shit. Actually I move 100 feet away so that I can be 70 feet from Theoseus, 'cause I had 140 movement.
DM: Okay. Uh, it is going to first, um, move 30 feet forward
DM: attempting to engulf Dalwath.
Kenzo: I'm already engulfed.
DM: Oh, you're already engulfed. Yeah, yeah.
DM: Dragging Dalwath with it.
Kenzo: [laughs]
DM: Uh, and then it is going to,
DM: um-
Kenzo: Oh, I didn't do that potion
DM: ... shoot a glob at, uh,
DM: Kenzo.
Kenzo: Okay.
Kenzo: Come at me.
DM: Uh,
DM: make a dex saving throw.
Kenzo: Uh, 21.
DM: Fails.
Kenzo: Reroll.
Seeker: Fuck. Four- uh, 16.
DM: Uh, you take 13 reduced to six points of acid damage and you are
DM: yanked back inside with Dalwath.
Kenzo: What? I'm restrained again?
Unknown: Wellby, come over here next to me.
DM: Uh, I forgot to mention though, it was bloodied on your last attack.
Kenzo: Oh, wow.
Unknown: Ah.
Kenzo: Wait, but on, on a... It can...
Kenzo: But why am I doing a dex save to get restrained?
DM: It has a, it has multiple attacks.
DM: It has a pseudopod attack and then it has a restraining glob attack that pulls you back into its body.
Kenzo: Bitch.
DM: And then it has a bonus action attack that did tons of damage to,
DM: um-
Wellby: So much damage.
Kenzo: Wellby.
DM: Oh, and then I keep forgetting it's totally chip damage.
DM: I keep forgetting the first time you do slashing damage in a turn you take acid damage.
DM: So...
DM: Oh, but- It's been a while since your turn.
DM: All these legend... It doesn't matter.
DM: Uh-
Unknown: It has been a while since Delwath's turn.
DM: Um, anyway, the ooze, uh,
DM: globs you, and then it's going to shoot a
DM: pseudopod at,
DM: uh, Wellby is the only one who is outside of it.
DM: That's a 23.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: And that's gonna do [laughs] 26 points of force damage.
Wellby: I will uncannily dodge it.
Unknown: That's 13.
DM: Yep.
Unknown: How many points you got left?
Unknown: 51.
DM: Um, and it does not get back its slime ejection.
Wellby: It also pushes it in, in attack.
Kenzo: Yeah. So all, all those pushages.
Kenzo: You didn't drink the fourth one. You saved the fourth one.
DM: So that, uh, that ends its turn.
DM: Gets its legendaries back.
Unknown: [laughs]
Unknown: Who's, who's next?
DM: Delwath is next.
Delwath: Okay. I'm gonna misty step outside it.
DM: Okay.
Unknown: Uh, which is bonus action.
DM: Uh, so who's...
DM: Kenzo was the last one who dealt damage to it, so it's resistant to bludgeoning.
Delwath: Um, so I don't know.
Delwath: How far away can I get from it with a misty step?
DM: Uh, you're like right at...
DM: You're pulled right within the edge, so you can get-
Delwath: Okay. So I can go... I'll misty step...
Delwath: Well, actually, it doesn't really matter. It, it hit you when you were 70 feet away, right?
Unknown: Yeah, 70 feet away.
DM: It's the range of all of its attack is 600 feet, so.
Unknown: Okay, so.
DM: Oh, except the only one that's not 600 feet is the, is the,
DM: the slime ejection.
Unknown: But that hit Wellby.
DM: Yes.
Delwath: So being 40 feet away versus 20 feet away makes no difference.
Delwath: Wait, the, uh, even the acid splash is 60 feet.
DM: The acid splash is 60 feet.
Delwath: Man, this thing's annoying. Okay. Uh, I will, I will bonus action misty step to be out of the restraint,
Unknown: and then I will attack it.
Delwath: First attack. I'm from 20 feet away at least.
DM: Okay.
Unknown: Little caution here.
Unknown: Uh, 20...
Unknown: Uh, wait. What's-
DM: Easy as 21
Delwath: ... what's 12 plus 7? That's 10.
Unknown: 19.
Unknown: 19. That misses.
DM: Uh, y- Oh, that misses, so you don't take damage.
Unknown: 20. Also misses.
Unknown: Yeah, you have to get a 22.
Unknown: 21 misses.
Delwath: That's nine. Okay. I will auto hit it on the last attack.
DM: Okay.
Unknown: And, and smite.
Kenzo: Nice. Nice. Nice. Get that smite in.
Unknown: How many times can you smite?
Unknown: Four.
Unknown: Sweet.
Unknown: With starting this level.
DM: Right.
Delwath: I used to be able to do three. Well, it takes a spell slot.
Unknown: Yeah. [laughs]
Delwath: So as long as I don't cast my spells for something else, but I misty stepped.
Unknown: I went sorcerer slot.
Delwath: So 28 plus, uh, 11.
DM: Uh, okay.
Unknown: I smited.
DM: That's your third smite.
Delwath: My third smite, okay. That's what I thought.
DM: Uh,
DM: you're doing damage to it. Uh-
Delwath: Oh, I need to remember, I can use my reaction to auto dodge.
DM: It is now gonna legend- it's now gonna use its first legendary action to crush.
Unknown: Fuck.
DM: So strength saves on you two.
Unknown: Damn it.
Unknown: 25.
Unknown: 18.
DM: Uh,
DM: Kenzo takes,
DM: uh, 26 points of force damage.
Delwath: [laughs] But you b- uh, l- Leviathan beats the save, so you take
DM: half that, so s- 13 points of force damage.
Delwath: Seeker's just like, "I'm gonna be a Leviathan."
Unknown: [laughs]
DM: [laughs] But it's gonna be pretty bad for Seeker,
DM: uh, if you, if you get forced out of your Leviathan form in the middle of the ooze.
Unknown: Right. That would be very bad.
DM: Uh, so let's hope that doesn't happen. That was its first legendary.
DM: After Delwath's turn, Seeker is up.
Delwath: You're still immune to... I guess you take a lot of acid damage.
Seeker: All right. So before my turn I will-
DM: No, it's not doing... It's just doing...
DM: It's not doing acid damage, it's just the immune to restrain is helping him a lot.
Seeker: Okay. I will close the last 30 feet to the bottom of the-
Unknown: That's the top.
Unknown: That's 50 feet.
DM: No, no, no.
Unknown: 30, 30, 30 to the bottom.
DM: He's, he's 30 feet to the bottom.
Unknown: Okay, cool.
Unknown: What do you see? What do you see when you-
Seeker: So before my turn I close the gap with my-
DM: So right now it's immune to bludgeoning, so that's a hard s- harder strength check.
Unknown: You have to make it.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: 'Cause it's...
Unknown: Oh, that's only a 15.
DM: Nope, you do not move.
Unknown: That's my legendary action.
DM: That's your legendary action. Now it's your turn.
DM: So you can try to move your turn.
Unknown: So you can try it again.
DM: But still, strength, strength check.
Unknown: That's much better.
Unknown: 24.
DM: Okay. 24, you push through,
DM: down to this,
DM: uh, incredibly hard crystal shell.
DM: There's like a 10-foot crystal shell at the-
Unknown: Oh, 10 feet.
DM: Yeah, and it's like the ooze, the matter of the ooze is, like, piling up down here and forming this.
DM: It's not actually really crystal, it's just super dense.
Seeker: Okay. What do, what do I do?
Unknown: [laughs] Um-
DM: It is... Oh, cherries.
Wellby: Break the shell with Leviathan.
Unknown: Yeah, maybe I try and smash it.
Unknown: Yeah, but it's, it's already...
Seeker: It, it's, um, resistant to bludgeoning right now, isn't it?
DM: It is currently-
Wellby: Is there a bludgeoning gap in the shell anywhere?
Unknown: Oh, can I go inside of it though?
DM: No.
Unknown: Hmm.
Unknown: Interesting idea.
DM: Yeah, it's currently resistant to bludgeoning.
Unknown: Hmm.
Unknown: I mean-
Unknown: Spell damage?
Seeker: That's gonna be the thing.
Unknown: Um...
Kenzo: I mean, you could just cast wish and end the whole battle right now.
Delwath: Can't use a scroll when you're controlled.
Unknown: Can't use scrolls.
Seeker: When I'm Leviathan. And I don't have a gap or an entrance
Unknown: to the-
Delwath: That's why you're a Leviathan, is 'cause...
Seeker: Okay. Telekinesis on an object could move it 30 feet.
Seeker: I could try to rip it out, but that's pretty far to go.
Unknown: Are you gonna crush it with telekinesis?
Delwath: Oh, wait. Leviathan's auto crit against objects.
Delwath: Or, like, do massive damage against objects.
Unknown: Uh, hold on.
Unknown: Um
Wellby: Double damage to objects and creatures
Unknown: Double damage
Unknown: Oh, siege monster
Unknown: Yeah
Unknown: Is an object?
Unknown: So not, not a crit.
Delwath: Just attack it. Even if it's, even with bludgeoning resistance, you're better off.
Delwath: You do double damage, that cancels...
Unknown: Use your attacks
Seeker: All right. All right. So then I'll just do my multi-attack, which is a slam and a tail-
Unknown: No, wait, make a tidal wave
Unknown: Oh.
Seeker: Yeah, so that's a DC 24 strength saving throw
Unknown: But, like, against an object?
Delwath: I don't know. Can you, like, make a massive blast of water from the middle of the leviathan?
DM: You can't make a tidal wave inside a creature
Unknown: Okay, fair enough
Unknown: [laughs]
Unknown: That's fair
Unknown: Tim, Tim makes the rules
Unknown: [laughs] No, that, that seems-
Unknown: Tim knows the rules
Unknown: That seems reasonable
Seeker: Yeah, the tidal wave was a good idea, but no, I get-
Unknown: No, just attack it
Seeker: ... a slam and a tail attack, so that's-
Unknown: Yes.
Delwath: You gotta roll, uh, you have a plus 14, so...
Delwath: You need an eight?
Unknown: 21 hit. No, 21 missed
DM: AC is 22
Unknown: Yeah, so you need eight.
Wellby: Nice, nice
Unknown: That's a nine and an eight
Unknown: So it's okay
Unknown: So-
DM: Oh, wait, wait. Which one are you doing first?
Unknown: 16 and an eight. Yeah.
Unknown: Um-
DM: The slam or the tail?
Seeker: Uh, I do the slam first, 'cause I'm facing it
DM: Okay
Seeker: And then I'll spin around and do the tail [laughs]
DM: So you, you slam into it, uh, striking this crystalline shell.
DM: And for
DM: a moment,
DM: you get, like, a flash of, a flashback, like, a Seeker flashback to Limbo, and it is completely immune to the damage you do
Unknown: Ugh
DM: The form that it is in is resistant to, immune to all damage except thunder, currently
Unknown: Thunder?
Unknown: Ugh
DM: But it's a fragment of Limbo
Wellby: Oh, so it must be constantly changing, maybe?
Unknown: So, so both my attacks are just
Unknown: repelled
DM: N- neither of your attacks do anything
Unknown: Wait, no, 'cause acid
DM: But it is a fragment of Limbo
Unknown: Yeah
Unknown: Tim
Unknown: So I just, I just-
Delwath: That is a clue. I don't know what kind of clue it is, but...
Kenzo: Tim, I just, uh, realized, uh, with Haste-
Wellby: Hit it with Order
Kenzo: With Haste I have, uh, advantage on dexterity saves
Wellby: Give it proofs
Unknown: I could... Oh, I can't put proofs of creation
Kenzo: So I failed once and then I, so I, I don't know, I won't-
DM: Eh, the last combat you were supposed to have disadvantage on dex saves, and you forgot about it, so-
Unknown: All right. All right
DM: ... it's even now-
Unknown: Can't do that
DM: ... but don't forget for the next one
Unknown: [laughs]
Wellby: Do we have anything from Mc- Me- McAnnis, Mechanicus, whatever it is?
Delwath: My sword's attuned to McAnnis.
Delwath: Wait, but, but you're not standing in...
Unknown: There's, there's not, like, a...
DM: No, this is inside the creature
Unknown: It's not like there's not-
DM: This is, like, its heart
DM: There's no, but there's not, like, some space to stand
DM: No, no, no, no,
DM: no
Unknown: Can you do thunder damage?
Unknown: Well, my turn is over
Unknown: Right, okay
DM: Uh, yeah. Seeker's turn is over and it's now gonna use a legendary resistance, um-
Unknown: Action
DM: Sorry, action. I keep saying resistance.
DM: Uh, with, now with you this close, it is, um, clearly getting quite nervous about...
DM: Or it's reacting to the presence of you here and it is going to,
DM: um, crush again.
DM: Uh, you have disadvantage on the strength save because you are so close to its heart
Unknown: Ugh.
Unknown: So
Unknown: Take a lot of damage
DM: Uh, Kenzo, you're also engulfed
Unknown: No, I-
DM: You need to make a strength save
Unknown: 17
DM: 17 fails.
DM: Um, so you take 26 points of force damage
Unknown: Oh, that's fine
Unknown: I have, you have to make a con save
DM: And Kenzo also takes 26 points of force damage
Delwath: 13. You have to roll a s- But not, don't roll one or two
Unknown: So I have to make a concentration save
DM: Concentration check, yep
Unknown: You have four legendary resistances
DM: Yeah
Delwath: Wait, why aren't you using... Well, it's probably not worth it, but...
DM: I would save your legendary resistances-
Unknown: Yeah
DM: ... for failing concentration saves
DM: So roll
Unknown: That's a three
Unknown: That's not a one or a two [laughs]
DM: So pass
DM: You're gonna get it.
Wellby: It's only a matter of time
Unknown: You're gonna pull it in
Wellby: That doesn't have to be a five or six
Unknown: Yeah [laughs]
DM: Uh-
Delwath: Seeker's gonna get nervous if I keep rolling a five or six
Unknown: [laughs]
Unknown: I'm liking it so far
DM: That ends Seeker's turn as we start the next round.
DM: Wellby is now 140 feet away, which is the furthest away you can be, as it's moved 30 feet closer.
DM: Um, the ooze is still moving slowly towards
DM: the edge of the mist, uh, trying to get Wellby, Kenzo, and Delweth.
DM: That are the three it can see, while Kenzo is currently engulfed and Delweth has been dodging out of the way, while Misty's stepping out of the way or using other magic, 'cause Delweth is almost impossible to restrain.
DM: Seeker, meanwhile, as the leviathan, is at its heart
DM: a fragment of Limbo which has currently taken the shape of a crystal immune to everything but for, but thunder damage
Seeker: Can you make a demiplane and then push it into the door?
Kenzo: [laughs] Push the heart into the door
Unknown: Or the mist
DM: And it is Wellby's turn
Wellby: I mean, we could put two extra dimensional spaces together right in the middle of it
Seeker: Oh, and just deaden it. Yeah
Wellby: Uh, okay.
Wellby: I am shooting.
Wellby: That is a 18, 1 and an 18.
Wellby: That's funny. Um...
DM: Okay.
DM: Shifts to Piercing at the end of Wellby's turn
Wellby: Uh, 10,
Wellby: 32, maker, 20, 35, 38, 46.
Wellby: And then I'm gonna drink a healing potion and then move 90 feet straight up
DM: Okay.
DM: Um, it is going to use its, uh, last legendary action, um, before its turn,
DM: uh, to fire a pseudopod at Wellby Um, that is a 19
Wellby: 19 just hits me.
Wellby: 19 is my AC.
DM: That's, uh, that's only 16 points of force damage.
DM: And now Kenzo is up.
DM: You are restrained.
DM: You take 24 points of force damage.
Kenzo: I'm almost dead.
Kenzo: Thanks.
DM: No, you're really far from being dead, 'cause if you drop to zero you actually only drop to-
Kenzo: You get
DM: ... 70-
Kenzo: Oh, yeah.
Kenzo: Yeah, yeah, yeah
DM: ... like 80-some high number.
Kenzo: I'm so glad I took that.
DM: [laughs]
Kenzo: Okay.
Unknown: Wait, what's the turn order?
Delwath: When does Kenzo go compared to Delwath?
DM: The ooze is in between the two of them.
Delwath: Okay, so it goes the two of them, the ooze, Delwath, then Seeker?
DM: Yep.
Kenzo: Yeah. In fact, I... How many times...
Kenzo: I, I can... Do I... Does that just keep happening?
DM: Every time you start your turn in the ooze you take force damage.
Kenzo: No, no, I know, but I mean, uh, um, the, uh...
Kenzo: I can... If I go down to zero and then I spend-
Unknown: Once
DM: No, it's once.
Kenzo: Once. Okay. All right. 'Cause I'm saving a...
Kenzo: I want to use my 10 hit dice too, but I'm gonna wait, wait for that until after I
Kenzo: die once.
DM: After you die once-
Kenzo: Yeah
DM: ... you could use the 10 D10 healing.
Kenzo: Yeah, exactly. Um, okay, cool.
Kenzo: In that case then, so now I've got three actions, a bonus action.
Kenzo: Can I have bonus action try to es- uh...
Kenzo: I have to use actions to get out of the restraint.
DM: No. It's, it has to be your haste action or your regular action.
Kenzo: All right. Ah, fucking bitch, man.
DM: I, I think your... I would...
DM: I mean, I think your odds of hitting-
Kenzo: Just stand here and fight him? Just-
DM: Fighting is not that... I mean, you, you're not gonna hit.
Kenzo: Yeah, but you might-
DM: But you make so many attacks
Delwath: ... you might be better off making six attacks.
DM: If you waste your whole turn doing no damage, if instead you make six attacks, you're almost certainly gonna hit on three of them.
DM: You're gonna hit for three of them. [sighs]
DM: And you get one au- You get one automatic free try without spending an action at the end of your turn.
Kenzo: That's true. All right.
Kenzo: I gotta stay in here and just fight, fight for a little while, 'cause yeah, that-
DM: Well, you could use your haste action.
Delwath: That's not a... No, no. Use your haste action to try and escape.
Unknown: Right.
DM: 'Cause there's only one attack.
Unknown: But at half value. At half value.
DM: It's not that valuable.
Kenzo: Okay. All right. All right. I'll use my haste action
Kenzo: to try to escape.
Delwath: 'Cause last turn you couldn't use your bonus action 'cause you tried with the haste potion, right?
DM: Yeah, correct.
DM: Yeah.
Kenzo: That fails. I will spend a ki to try again.
Kenzo: 18 still fails, right?
DM: Yeah. 18 fails.
Kenzo: [coughs] All right, I'm still in there.
Kenzo: So now
Kenzo: the idea is to attack twice with a disadvantage?
DM: Well, you can attack five times, 'cause you have-
Kenzo: Five
DM: ... your bonus action attack too.
Kenzo: Right. Um-
DM: But each attack is with disadvantage.
Kenzo: All right. Why the fuck not? Let's, let's give it a go.
Kenzo: First attack.
Kenzo: That hits.
DM: Yeah. Yeah.
Kenzo: Um, second attack.
Kenzo: That misses.
Kenzo: Third attack.
Kenzo: That misses. Fourth attack.
Kenzo: That misses.
DM: [laughs] That was-
Kenzo: Fifth attack. That misses.
Kenzo: [laughs]
DM: Wow, you do-
Unknown: That was brutal
DM: ... 2 D12.
Kenzo: 2 D12 plus, uh, nine.
DM: Plus s- plus nine.
Kenzo: 15.
DM: 20.
Kenzo: Or 24.
Delwath: 15 plus 9. Yeah, 24.
Kenzo: And now I, I roll one more time.
DM: Now you get one sa- strength save.
Kenzo: I'm just gonna roll them at the same time like I have advantage, 'cause I do.
DM: Well, no, because it costs you ki.
Unknown: You don't... Oh.
Kenzo: No, I don't... Dude, I still have, I still have, I still have, like, I still have, I still have-
DM: Well, each Flurry of Blows also costs you ki.
Wellby: Do you have, like, 20 ki at this point?
DM: Yeah, you have 20 ki.
Kenzo: Yeah.
DM: So you're probably not gonna run out, but-
Kenzo: No, no, I'm still good. I, I'm still gonna try.
DM: Okay.
Kenzo: All right. Well, I'll s- I'll roll the first one first.
Unknown: You just roll one attack-
Kenzo: Yeah
Unknown: ... 'cause you might escape
Kenzo: ... 'cause I might escape.
Unknown: On the first.
Kenzo: Fuck. Did not escape.
Kenzo: Did not escape. Ugh.
Kenzo: Damn.
DM: That ends Kenzo's turn.
Kenzo: Ouch.
DM: Um, the ooze is up.
DM: So, sorry, Wellby, how far are you away?
Wellby: 165 feet.
DM: Okay. How far is Delwath away?
Unknown: Uh...
DM: Like 20 feet?
Unknown: 20...
Kenzo: You're 20 feet.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: So it's gonna move 30 feet and try and engulf Delwath.
DM: Strength saving throw.
Delwath: Wait, my... Why roll? What's the DC?
DM: Uh, 23.
Delwath: I can't actually make it. It's impossible for Delwath to make a DC.
DM: Did you already use your-
Unknown: I haven't used the-
DM: ... favor of the...
Unknown: Yes
DM: ... So if you roll high you could use...
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: Okay. Delwath is engulfed.
Delwath: No, it's easier honestly to just get engulfed.
DM: To just get out.
Unknown: This time I'll get us both out.
Kenzo: How do you do that?
Unknown: Scatter.
Kenzo: Oh my God.
Wellby: Oh.
Kenzo: Thank you, fucking Delwath.
Kenzo: Jesus Christ.
DM: Um-
Kenzo: 'Cause now that I'm out again it needs to do dexterity saves for me.
Unknown: Yeah.
Kenzo: And I have haste, so I can... I will, I will make those.
DM: Well, no, the engulf is a strength save.
DM: The restraining glob that pulls you in from a distance is dex.
Kenzo: I know, but if I'm, if I'm far away-
DM: If you're far away, then the dex saves are-
Kenzo: Exactly
DM: ... yeah.
Delwath: Exactly. Which I want to be, so.
DM: Um, so, uh, all it can do is pseudopod on,
DM: um... Sorry, you're 170 you said?
Wellby: 165.
DM: So you're too far away for the restraining glob.
Kenzo: This might take it down.
Wellby: Surely it can attack someone else.
DM: So it's gonna attack you twice.
Wellby: Awesome.
DM: Everybody else is inside it. All it can do is crush them to death.
Unknown: I'm gonna get us out this time.
Unknown: I only have one more-
DM: So that's a 20-
Unknown: After that I-
Kenzo: I'm not gonna get back in there
DM: ... one and a 30-something
Kenzo: ... I'm not, I'm not gonna get...
Kenzo: I'm, I'm not gonna get back in there again.
Wellby: It presumably has
Wellby: blindsight.
Unknown: [laughs] Yeah, it's not great.
DM: Yeah, it has-
Unknown: I, I've, I've wore, I've wore darkvision
DM: ... 600 feet of blindsight.
Unknown: Yeah, yeah, you'll be fine.
Wellby: I'll be fine.
Unknown: Delwath will not.
DM: Uh, 19 force and then 22 force with the second.
Wellby: Each of those is an attack.
DM: Yeah.
Wellby: Uh, I'll uncanny dodge the second one.
DM: Okay.
Wellby: So that's total of 30.
Wellby: Awesome. I'm down to 23.
DM: Um, and then it's... Does it get its bonus action back?
DM: Nope.
DM: It is not going to spray slime.
DM: That, uh, ends its turn.
Unknown: So Delwath?
DM: So Delwath is up.
DM: You take 21-
Delwath: Wait, wait, wait, hold on. Voluntory action. Voluntory action.
DM: Oh, yeah.
Seeker: What? I could move or slam attack.
Delwath: Why don't you hit the orb again? Is it still...
Delwath: Oh, do you know if its resistance has changed?
Kenzo: Is there any way to tell?
Unknown: What, what's the resistance? Yeah.
DM: It, the physical appearance of the orb has not changed.
Kenzo: I think so. It probably has not changed.
DM: Uh, the, the thing itself is resistant-
Unknown: Wait
DM: ... to bludgeoning
Unknown: ... punch the outside.
Unknown: Don't attack the heart.
Kenzo: Touch, touch the ooze.
Unknown: Just punch those-
Kenzo: Touch the ooze, yeah.
Unknown: Yeah.
Kenzo: Yeah.
Seeker: So I do my, my usual slam attack.
Unknown: Just, I mean it's resist-
DM: Well, right now it's resistant to bludgeoning.
Delwath: So what? You can still do 10 damage.
DM: Yeah.
Delwath: It's not gonna hurt it. I mean, it's not...
Wellby: It must be headed towards like a quarter or so.
Unknown: Yeah.
Unknown: It's gonna tip away.
DM: It's, it's very close to a quarter.
Unknown: It did not. I rolled a three, so.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: So that misses.
Unknown: Okay.
DM: Uh, Delweth, you take...
Unknown: 22, you said
DM: ... 22 points of force damage at the start of your turn.
Delwath: I'm not in love with the number of hit points I have left.
Kenzo: Mm.
DM: But 75, I'll be okay.
Wellby: Ugh, I dream of having 75 hit points.
Unknown: [laughs]
Delwath: Yeah. Uh, bonus action, use metamagic to quicken Scatter.
Kenzo: Oh, thank God.
DM: Okay.
Delwath: Kenzo and Delweth both appear anywhere you'd like within 120 feet.
Kenzo: Uh, I'm gonna be... I'm gonna get myself fucking away from this motherfucker.
Kenzo: Uh, I'm gonna get... Oh, 70 feet again.
Unknown: Yeah, I'm gonna be-
Kenzo: So I can attack and come back
Unknown: ... 20 feet away
Delwath: and then I will...
Delwath: So I'm out of metamagics.
Kenzo: This is a great combat though, 'cause this is definitely very challenging.
Delwath: And I will just attack it.
Unknown: Let's see. I used
Unknown: Scatter.
Unknown: Oh, I could always Plane Shift.
Delwath: I could just, I could go to the Feywild if I really thought I would die otherwise.
DM: Yeah.
Delwath: Or somewhere. I could go back to Limbo, that doesn't sound wise.
Unknown: Um.
Unknown: [coughs]
Unknown: Okay. I am gonna-
DM: Well, that was your bonus, so you still have your action.
Unknown: Yep. Yep.
Kenzo: You still have your standard, your dash. Your dash move.
Delwath: I am just going to attack.
Unknown: Oh, the soil.
DM: Yeah.
Seeker: But I'm in leviathan form.
Unknown: I know, I was saying, is there a reason for me to use-
Delwath: First attack is a 20
Unknown: ...
Unknown: the dirt?
Unknown: Uh, 22.
Unknown: You're right, yeah.
DM: 22, yep.
DM: 'Cause I'm in leviathan form so I can access to my-
DM: Right.
Delwath: Second attack is a 23.
DM: I mean, it's a piece of Limbo.
Delwath: Third attack crits. Another crit smite.
Unknown: Last-
DM: Good
Unknown: ... piece of Limbo.
Unknown: Last spell slot
Seeker: ... what I can do is-
Kenzo: Lots of damage
Delwath: Okay. So that's six.
DM: What do you, what do you do to Limbo?
DM: What's-
Unknown: Control is my mind?
Unknown: Uh.
Unknown: But I have to be inside of it?
Delwath: Wait, I hit with all attacks, that's two-
Unknown: Maybe I just like get up-
Unknown: Four
Unknown: ...
Unknown: and wrap my tentacles around it
Unknown: ... 12. 12 plus four
Delwath: is 16, plus 20.
Unknown: And
Seeker: can... And what do I imagine?
Unknown: Just, just like...
Kenzo: You've got, you've got imagination dirt in your pocket.
DM: Delweth does...
Unknown: Ah.
Unknown: 5, 10, 15.
Delwath: 99 plus 15 plus 18.
Unknown: Hell yeah.
Wellby: Holy shit. In one attack?
Unknown: Three attacks.
Kenzo: Wow.
DM: Uh, it's b- it's below a quarter.
Delwath: I mean, that was a crit and my last...
Delwath: I critted twice and smited on crits twice.
Kenzo: Dude, 120.
Unknown: That's 20 D8.
DM: So Delweth-
Unknown: Oh, then I run away.
DM: How far away are you?
Unknown: I'm 20 feet from
Unknown: it.
DM: But after you run away, how far?
Delwath: Oh, after I run away, uh, I am...
DM: Uh, you also take five points of acid damage.
Delwath: After I run away, I'm 20 plus 60.
DM: Okay. Well, you're...
DM: I mean, you actually technically haven't left its reach, 'cause its reach is 600.
DM: So it's not gonna have an opportunity to attack you.
Delwath: Well, no, I mean just the engulf.
DM: Yeah, yeah. It's, you're out of the range of engulf.
DM: Um, it is going to use a legendary action to use its grasping blob on Delweth, who just attacked it.
Unknown: That's an attack.
DM: Dex saving throw.
Unknown: One.
Kenzo: [laughs] No.
DM: Uh-
Kenzo: Oh, no
DM: ... you take 21 points of acid damage and you are back in the blob.
Kenzo: Dude, this thing is gnarly as fuck.
Delwath: I'm, I'm not in good shape here, guys.
Unknown: Please kill it.
Kenzo: I mean, we're probably gonna do it next round.
DM: Uh, that was its legendary. Seeker's up.
Kenzo: I'm, I'm gonna fuck it up this round.
Unknown: All right.
Kenzo: I'm gonna fuck it up.
Unknown: I can get out...
Unknown: I can get out twice more.
Kenzo: I know where, we're gonna kill it. You, that, that has my-
Unknown: I only have 45 hit points left
Kenzo: ... we're gonna fuck him up this turn.
Unknown: I will use my action
Unknown: to reach out
Seeker: and... What kind of limbs does the, does this leviathan even have?
Unknown: Or reach out with my-
DM: You just shape whatever you want out of water
Seeker: ... ah, reach out with my enormous flippers and give this thing kind of like a,
Seeker: a hug. 'Cause it's, I'm huge, but this is also huge.
DM: Yeah.
Kenzo: How big is the thing, the object?
DM: 10 foot... It's a crystal s- shell that's like a 10-foot,
DM: uh, diameter sphere.
Seeker: And just focus my mind and all my energy on it
Seeker: vanishing into a poof of feathers.
Delwath: What are you... Are you just literally trying to manipulate Limbo?
Unknown: I'm just using, using my-
DM: Make an intelligence check
Unknown: ... which is, uh...
Unknown: Oh, with the leviathan-
DM: It's your own intelligence
Unknown: ... your stats, your intelligence
DM: ... it's your, your shape change, so you get your stats, your mental stats.
Unknown: But I'm using the leviathan's... Oh, it's mental stats.
Delwath: Physically. You get your mental and its physical.
DM: Yeah.
Seeker: Oh, so that's the plus five.
Unknown: All right.
Unknown: That's a 15.
Unknown: 10 plus 5.
DM: Uh.
Unknown: I can heroic it.
DM: Um,
DM: nothing happens.
Delwath: It could... I mean, 50/50 chance of doing better than 10.
Unknown: This might be worth heroicing.
Unknown: Wait, you're trying to turn it into feathers?
Seeker: I just want it to vanish, yeah.
Unknown: I don't know. I didn't... If anybody has a better idea.
Kenzo: No, feathers, feathers are great.
Delwath: I mean, try and... I would think try and turn it into something fragile so that your bludgeoning attack can hurt it.
Unknown: Oh.
Delwath: Trying to change its resistance might be easier than making it go away.
Unknown: Well-
Unknown: But
Unknown: ... I did what I did.
Kenzo: Feathers are fragile.
Unknown: Yeah, yeah, feathers are fragile.
Unknown: Okay. Okay, I'll use my heroic.
Unknown: Yeah.
Unknown: Reroll.
Unknown: No, that's way worse.
DM: Nope, you do not change it.
Unknown: Leviathan.
Kenzo: You can bonus action attack it now, right?
DM: Does leviathan have bonus actions?
DM: No.
Wellby: You can't legendary after your own turn
DM: ... So that ends Seeker's turn.
DM: Um, it will,
DM: uh, legendary after
DM: Seeker to crush you.
DM: So disadvantage on the strength save, that's 22 points of force damage.
DM: D- roll a strength save with disadvantage.
DM: I think you're the only one inside it now, right?
Kenzo: Yeah.
Delwath: I think we had been in just engulfed Delwath.
DM: Oh, it just engulfed Delwath. So same thing, strength save for you.
Kenzo: That's a three.
Delwath: Um, Delwath was probably gonna die guys.
Unknown: I need some help.
Delwath: How many points is that?
Kenzo: 25?
Unknown: [coughs]
Kenzo: Nope.
DM: What did you roll?
Kenzo: A three. I'm done.
DM: So you take 21, you take 21.
Unknown: I have 20 hit points.
DM: Um, that's the second legendary.
Unknown: Yeah, it's 23. I'm not at the bottom anymore.
Kenzo: Well, I actually had 20.
Unknown: No.
DM: Uh, Wellby is-
Unknown: I'm not at the bottom
DM: ... is on the top of the order.
DM: Um,
DM: and currently now Seeker is trying to shift this
DM: knot of limbo into something that is not immune to all damage but thunder.
Kenzo: Yeah, but you can put out one.
Unknown: I know, I know, but how many of us here?
DM: 23.
Kenzo: Wow, what a club.
Unknown: [laughs] And 400.
DM: [laughs]
Unknown: Do you have anything for healing?
Delwath: Yeah, I c- I have healing potions and I, well, I can cast a second level healing word.
DM: Delwath is engulfed.
DM: Yeah, put y- put yourself in there if you're engulfed, so I can tell.
DM: Kenzo is not engulfed.
Kenzo: I'm 70 feet away.
DM: 70 feet away. Wellby is 165 feet away.
DM: And it's Wellby's turn to attack.
Unknown: I do that.
Wellby: I shoot it, and that's a 20...
Wellby: It's almost, like, s- like a 30 or something.
DM: That hits.
Kenzo: Let's just fucking kill it.
DM: So-
Unknown: Oh, no.
Unknown: That's poor rolling.
Unknown: 10. 15.
Unknown: That's terrible.
Unknown: 25, 33.
Wellby: 33. And then, uh, second shot, uh, hits.
Wellby: And it's another nine, so that's 42 altogether.
DM: Got it.
Delwath: Can you use your, like, lightning arrow or something?
DM: He already used it.
Wellby: No, I already used it.
Unknown: Um,
Unknown: and I don't think it can be restrained.
DM: It is immune to restraint, yeah.
Wellby: Um, and then I'll move another 90 feet.
DM: So you're gonna mo- Oh, straight up.
DM: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: So you're going up in the clear sky.
DM: So now you're quite far away from it.
DM: But you're still within 600 feet, and you attacked it last, so it's gonna use its last legendary to pseudopod shot you.
DM: Oh,
DM: that's a natural 20.
Kenzo: Oh, fuck.
Unknown: That's a long way to fall.
Kenzo: Oh, shit.
DM: Uh, you take
DM: 69-
Wellby: Probably this other call auto kicks in if you're in the air
Delwath: ... C- can you, you can, you can dodge it.
Unknown: Oh, I can.
Kenzo: Right?
Unknown: I can.
DM: So that's 10, 26.
Wellby: It has to be less than... It has to be 45 or fewer.
DM: 26.
Kenzo: That's what I think.
DM: Um, plus eight is 34.
Kenzo: Oh, that's actually pretty sick.
Unknown: 34.
DM: Plus eight is 42.
Kenzo: That's great.
Unknown: Awesome.
DM: One hit point.
Unknown: That works. [laughs]
Kenzo: I'm going again?
DM: Twice.
Wellby: On any dodge, I have
Unknown: two hit points.
Delwath: Two hit points. Damn. No, that's like twice what I thought.
DM: It is now resistant.
Unknown: [laughs]
DM: It is now res-
Kenzo: I said twice as many hit points as you thought.
Unknown: Yeah
DM: ... It is now resistant to piercing and Kenzo is up.
Kenzo: All right. Now I'm gonna fuck this motherfucker up.
Unknown: Do you have any healing that heals all of us?
Kenzo: So I get six attacks now, right?
DM: No.
Kenzo: Or-
DM: Yeah
Kenzo: ... six, right?
Kenzo: Yeah, 'cause I get three staff attacks-
DM: Yep
Kenzo: ... three, three, um...
Kenzo: But these are just regular attacks. There's no advantage or anything else going on.
Kenzo: But still, let's fucking go.
Kenzo: Okay, so these are all plus 15.
Kenzo: 20, 20 misses, right?
DM: 20 misses.
Kenzo: 20 misses.
Unknown: 20.
Kenzo: Okay, so two, two staff attacks hit, and then three unarmed strikes.
Kenzo: Ooh, a crit.
Unknown: Ooh, crit.
Kenzo: Uh, I have a crit.
Unknown: A miss and a hit.
Kenzo: A miss and a hit. Yeah, so.
DM: So two staffs and a crit, and a hit.
DM: So that's three D12 on the staffs-
Kenzo: And three
DM: ... two D12 on the hit, on the crit.
DM: 6 D12 total.
Unknown: 6 D12 plus-
Kenzo: Plus
Unknown: ... you had three hits.
Delwath: So 6 D12 plus, uh-
Kenzo: Oh, no
Unknown: ...
Delwath: uh, plus nine plus 12.
Kenzo: Pl- plus, plus 18.
DM: Two staff and two-
Kenzo: Minus, two staffs
DM: ... plus 18 plus 14.
Kenzo: Plus 18.
Unknown: Wait, both your staffs hit?
Kenzo: Two out of three staffs.
DM: He has three staffs on the haste.
Kenzo: I'm hasted. I'm hasted.
DM: Okay, roll your 6 D12.
Kenzo: So it's 6 D12 plus what?
DM: I got it, plus 18 plus 12.
Kenzo: I, I know. I like to know. I wanna know.
Kenzo: I wanna-
DM: 6 D12 plus 18 plus 14.
Kenzo: Okay, 6 D12. All right, fucking die.
Unknown: 12 plus 32.
Kenzo: Fucking die.
Delwath: Wait, don't you get two D12 on... Don't you get a bonus D12 on the first staff that hits?
Kenzo: I do.
DM: Yeah, yeah. So-
Kenzo: D12
DM: ... so three D12 on the staff.
Kenzo: For two hits.
DM: For two hits, and three D12 on the-
Kenzo: And for the crit
DM: ... punches for two hits.
Kenzo: Yeah. Okay, yeah, that's right.
Kenzo: Fucking die, motherfucker.
Wellby: Big numbers. Yeah, okay.
Kenzo: That's good.
Unknown: Oh, that's 12. That's 12. That's good.
Kenzo: Okay, so hold on. 20, 30,
Kenzo: 38,
Kenzo: 42.
Unknown: Plus 32.
Kenzo: 42 plus 32.
Unknown: Well, plus the 15 plus-
Kenzo: Yeah
Delwath: ... 18 that ti- or 14 plus 18.
DM: I got it. It's looking pretty weak.
Kenzo: Close. Oh, yeah, so I go in 70 feet and then I come out 70 feet.
Kenzo: So I'm at, I stay 70 feet away.
DM: Uh, yeah, it moves seven, it moves 30 feet in your direction.
DM: It can't engulf you, but it can shoot two pseudopods at you.
Kenzo: Come at me. Come at me with your pseudopods.
DM: That's a
DM: 26-
Kenzo: That hits
DM: ... and a 24.
Kenzo: They both hit.
DM: Okay. So the first one is going to do...
DM: Ooh, that's a good damage roll. 36 points of damage, force damage.
Kenzo: So, so basically, like, you see, like, this thing, it shoots, like, right through Kenzo's heart.
Kenzo: He's like, "Ah, I'm dead."
Kenzo: And then like s- Kenzo magically revitalizes me [laughs].
DM: [laughs]
Kenzo: All right. I'm so glad I took that fucking hit point thing.
DM: So-
Kenzo: Yeah
Delwath: You at half of the hit points now
Kenzo: ... uh, so now I'm back to 50%, so whatever 174 over...
Kenzo: Oh, actually no. It wouldn't be the temporary.
Kenzo: Half of my original, right?
Kenzo: Not like-
DM: No, it's just whatever your hit point maximum, so you're at 87.
Unknown: Yeah.
Kenzo: Okay. Fuck yeah. Great.
Kenzo: Nice.
Kenzo: All right.
Delwath: Yeah, the age doesn't go away for eight hours.
DM: Yeah.
Kenzo: All right, great.
Unknown: Or until you die.
Kenzo: So I'm back at 87.
Unknown: You capacity it does.
DM: And then the second one is 21.
Kenzo: Okay. So I still take that 21 damage.
DM: Well, unless you reaction block it.
Kenzo: Yeah, of course I would... I'd do that.
Kenzo: So now I'm good.
DM: So you take none.
Kenzo: A- and then now it does a DC 20.
Kenzo: Oh, maybe I can kill it here.
DM: N- uh, yeah, it fails.
Kenzo: Oh, it fails. Cool. So it, uh, it now-
DM: Well,
DM: h- badly hurt. It still has over 100 hit points.
Kenzo: Okay.
DM: It's just like around 100.
Kenzo: I'm gonna... Who's next?
Unknown: Delwath.
Kenzo: Hold on. Hold on. Hold on.
DM: Uh, Delwath is next, yeah.
Kenzo: Seven plus seven, so it does 14 more damage.
DM: Okay.
Kenzo: Okay.
DM: So it
DM: is finished with its turn as Delwath moves
DM: to escape.
Unknown: So-
DM: Uh, wait. First you take 14 points of force damage
Unknown: ... why are you doing this?
Kenzo: Just-
Delwath: Okay. Um, so [laughs] here's the thing.
Unknown: Um, is there... Is...
Delwath: Wow, that's pretty amazing.
Unknown: Um,
Delwath: uh, m, do we...
Unknown: Are we gonna... I...
Kenzo: Are we what?
Delwath: I guess I can't really effectively run away.
DM: I mean, unless you run into the ash where it can't see you.
Unknown: Wait.
Wellby: It can't see us in the ash? This has been an option the entire time?
DM: I mean,
DM: I can see you 'cause it has blind sight, but it might not care about you so much.
Unknown: [sighs]
DM: If you just don't attack it, it's not gonna attack you.
DM: It's easy to run away.
Kenzo: We're so close to killing it, guys.
Delwath: I know. It's just I won't survive another hit.
Kenzo: Yeah.
Delwath: I can bonus action misty step out.
Kenzo: Cool.
Delwath: But then I don't have a lot of...
Delwath: I mean, I could just attack it and hope to kill it.
Kenzo: Can you smite again?
Unknown: Nah, I'm out of smites.
Kenzo: Ah, that sucks. Smite would've been good.
Unknown: Yeah.
Wellby: You- you're gonna drop at the end of your turn.
Unknown: I'm gonna drop at the end of my turn.
Unknown: Kenzo's gonna drop at the end of his turn.
DM: No, no. Kenzo's back to 87.
Unknown: Kenzo's gonna revive.
Kenzo: Yeah.
DM: He's all good.
Unknown: Kenzo's gonna revive us all.
Delwath: Wait, you have a key that can bring the dead back, right?
Kenzo: I do.
Unknown: Ah, screw it. [laughs]
Kenzo: [laughs]
Unknown: If I die, if I die, bring me back.
Kenzo: Yeah, yeah, of course. No, but that's only...
Kenzo: Die, like you have to use all, all your death saving throws too, right?
Unknown: Yeah, yeah.
Kenzo: Yeah.
Unknown: If that's likely.
Kenzo: I can bring, I can bring you back.
Wellby: If we both die, though. [laughs]
Unknown: [laughs]
Wellby: If we both die, [laughs] then...
DM: Then one of you is counting on the scroll of wish.
Unknown: Uh, but you can't cast...
Delwath: Oh, you can cast regular resurrection with wish.
Unknown: You don't need actual resurrection.
DM: Yeah, yeah.
Delwath: I will bonus action misty step,
Unknown: then I will attack it.
DM: Okay.
Kenzo: Hell yeah, dude. Fucking finish it off.
Unknown: Yeah. [laughs]
Kenzo: Let's go.
Unknown: Bonus. Epic.
Kenzo: I like this. I like this.
DM: It's gonna attack you, but that's fine.
Kenzo: We go for the win.
Unknown: Uh, that hits.
Unknown: Yes, it does.
Unknown: I mean,
Delwath: hopefully it'll be dead before its turn.
Kenzo: Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Unknown: Yeah.
Unknown: You're gonna kill it.
DM: Yeah, it just cast its-
Unknown: You're gonna kill it right now
DM: ... it's three legendaries, which just-
Unknown: That misses
Unknown: Do you have any inspirations left?
Delwath: I used my inspiration. I used my heroic.
Delwath: I can add a 2d8, a 2d4, but that won't make it one into a hit.
Unknown: Oh my God.
Kenzo: Whoa.
Unknown: Is that two ones?
Kenzo: Was that two ones in a row?
Unknown: No, that's two ones in a row.
Kenzo: That's insane. Man.
Unknown: That is one hit.
DM: You should use your mechanist ability.
DM: I mean, you can't now 'cause you already rolled, but-
Unknown: I can't now. Oh, I didn't think of that
DM: ... it's, it's in the sweet spot of AC where that ability is very strong
Unknown: I, I meant to use it. I meant to use it on...
Delwath: I actually meant to use it after my first failure.
Delwath: I, my, my rule is I'm supposed to use it after I fail.
DM: Fail once, right.
Delwath: My th- on my third attack, I've always used it.
DM: You use it, yeah.
Delwath: But I forgot to say that even though that's what I meant, so I guess...
Unknown: Ah.
Kenzo: Fair enough.
Unknown: It's only an extra 1d8-
DM: Right
Unknown: ... damage.
Unknown: We got this. We got this.
Unknown: Seven plus...
Delwath: Actually, it's an extra 1d8 plus 11.
DM: Yeah.
Delwath: So seven, that's 16, uh, 16.
Unknown: Seven, 18. 18.
DM: Okay. Well, it's-
Unknown: Uh
DM: ... it's, it's below 100 now.
Delwath: Yeah, but [laughs] that's not-
Unknown: It's not
Unknown: ... that wasn't-
Unknown: ... it's not as small of a number as we want it to say
DM: ... um, and now resistant to slashing.
Unknown: Uh.
DM: But you've been quite good at never doubling the same attack.
Unknown: There's really n-
Unknown: We can do 100 between the two of us
Unknown: ... nothing I can do.
Kenzo: Yeah. We'll live.
DM: So here comes the pseudopod.
Unknown: Is that attack roll?
DM: Yeah.
Unknown: Okay.
DM: Um, that's a 29.
Unknown: I will... Okay.
Delwath: Gotta roll a four or higher.
Kenzo: For what?
Delwath: To dodge it automatically with Tanji's, with the Tanji blessing.
Wellby: Come on, Tanji blessing.
Unknown: [laughs]
DM: Try again. [laughs]
Unknown: [laughs] Oh, no.
Kenzo: Three straight ones.
DM: Three straight ones doesn't seem fair.
DM: 30 points of force damage.
Unknown: Shalub goes down.
DM: As the pseudopod smacks into Delwath.
DM: That's one legendary action down.
DM: Seeker is up.
Kenzo: Um, all right.